It's time to get up!
Time to get up! Time to get up!
I can't eat any more...
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Story of the Girl's Dormitory"
Good morning!
Morning, Utae.
Good morning, Narukara-san.
Are you awake?
Good morning...
The boys' dorm gets dried fish,
natto, and raw egg.
And the girls get all this?
Huh? You're not going to eat any more?
I'm on a diet!
I heard Eri-chan got asked out.
By whom?
Mana-chan.
No way!
The sticker on your
phone is really cute.
Want to see my wallpaper?
It's really crazy!
Let's see...
It's my...
It's my pussy cat!
Oh, no! No way!
Who dropped that?
That was close...
I had no idea girls were so open,
when guys aren't around.
It kind of freaks me out!
What are you doing?
You're invisible. You don't need to run.
But, Chief...
Why do you think I gave
you that stealth suit?
I want you to use your talents
as a genius porno author
to write about the things that
happen in a girls' dorm.
Where did you get this thing?
eBay.
Taketo! Don't let yourself lose control!
I-I'm not!
Jeez...
A good novel is the product of
a lot of real-world research.
I'm counting on you, sensei.
I'll do my best.
Good morning. I brought breakfast.
Thank you.
It's really bad for you to stay
locked in your room,
without eating breakfast.
What are you hacking now?
The Pentagon's ICBM control system.
They've been really easy
to break into lately.
You were up all night, too?
Yeah, I'm working on a new rocket.
So I want to make sure no one
else has the same idea...
Right, right. The NASA database...
It was a scene that
could be found anywhere.
But not something that
just anyone could see.
There was a raw eros!
Oh, no. The laundry...
I can't get it up.
Once this is done, okay?
What do you think, Shimon-chan?
This is definitely human blood.
Tegakari Shimon
Genius
Forensic
Analyst!!
I-I saw this weird shadow.
And then blood just started
appearing from thin air...
That's like something
out of a horror story.
Someone's scaring my
little sister in broad daylight.
They've got guts, whoever they are...
You got an air mail.
Thank you.
It's amazing that you got
a letter from overseas!
Where's it from?
France. The Paris Conservatory
Music Institute.
They sent me one earlier.
They probably want me to attend.
Th-That's great!
Good luck there! I'll
be thinking of you!
I don't think I'll go.
Wh-Why not?
I'm not good enough yet.
And lately...
What's wrong?
Huh? Nothing...
Attention, all residents
of the girls' dorm.
Anyone seeing a translucent shadow
is to report to Beni
Botan-senpai immediately.
Repeat.
Anyone seeing a translucent shadow
is to report to Beni Botan...
This is bad... I'll hide here for a bit.
How dirty...
So this is what women are
really like, isn't it?
And they haven't been washed yet!
What kind of weirdo gets excited
by dirty underwear?
What are you saying, Ritsu?
Whether they're washed makes a huge
difference in their value!
You haven't changed your underwear
in three days, have you?
C-Captain, what are you...
I can tell.
It's a captain's job to know
everything about his crew.
U-Um...
Recently, I've been on
one flight after another.
I'm sorry...
There's no need to apologize.
The sweat and scent soaked into them testifies
to your worth as a stewardess.
Their value is far greater than any
freshly washed underwear.
Captain!
Let me have a better look.
I-It makes me want to write
something about that...
Senpai, what's going on?
It looks like an evil spirit
is wandering around.
A translucent shadow was slouched over,
holding my underwear!
A-A slouched-over evil spirit?
That's scary! Slouching is too scary!
I can feel it...
An evil soul, fallen to the land of lust
and ghosts after too long without sex.
That's so unscientific...
We must destroy this perverted spirit
for our little sisters.
We have to make it pay.
But how do we get rid of it?
We've got an expert on our side.
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Let me handle all your
evil spirit problems!
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Kagura Mai
Genius
Exorcist
Saint Maria
Genius
Exorcist
Punishment will be given
to the lost lambs.
I see. They're perfect.
Aren't they?
Good luck, you guys.
My only talent is computers,
so all I can do is wish you luck.
Ran-san...
It's fine. But let me do this.
Hey, Ran-chan.
We're too busy to be
seducing them right now...
I can't take this...
I'm seeing a darker evil aura now.
What's going on?
Wasn't this suit supposed to make it
so no one could see me?
When you get excited,
the stealth function begins to fail.
When the suit's shape changes,
the optic reflective surface's
cross-section area changes, too.
And the RCS formula, which depends
on electric field intensity
at optic angle of incidence, as well
as reflective scattering effect...
I have no idea what you're talking
about! This really sucks!
Sucks? You're sucking my...
Taketo, what are you...
Th-The formula, Ritsu!
3.14...
In other words, when part of the suit starts
to protrude, changing the shape,
the stealth function begins to degrade.
P-Protrude? You mean...
Just make sure it doesn't.
That's not the issue here!
L-Let's call this off! I'm leaving!
This is your time to shine!
To open the door to lust, without
letting yourself fall through...
I know that you can do it,
genius porno author Akutagawa Taketo!
This is a revolution!
You will journey through the girls' dorm,
previously off-limits to men,
and begin a new era, as
a pornographic author!
A porno revolution...
I'll do it. I'll do it!
Being an idol is really hard...
She has to take lessons
like this on her day off.
Good luck, Utae-san.
Leotards are just workout clothes.
Or they're supposed to be.
From now on, you'll practice in this.
I can't. I'm too embarrassed...
It's your stage outfit.
An idol should be aware that
her fans are watching.
An idol...
W-Watch me onstage!
I can't hold back anymore!
The ecstasy of it biting into
her behind was driving her mad.
It was no longer a lesson. It was a performance
for the men watching her!
I'm sorry, Utae-san.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I couldn't resist the
author's soul inside me...
But what is this? I feel like I'm too excited,
even for being in the girls' dorm.
I didn't see her naked.
So far, with the right circumstances, I could've
seen everything somewhere else.
Why is it so exciting?
This is...
It's such a normal sight,
yet it excites me.
It's because they all
have their guards down!
An exposed, open eros,
as part of everyday life.
This is it! This...
I think I've reached a new level
as a porno author!
I think I'm starting to
understand my revolution!
I love Sundays. You can
take a bath at noon!
It's really nice, isn't it?
This is an everyday eros, too.
Isn't it?
It was the slouching demon again, huh?
This is blood too, right?
It's hard to read, but it seems to be
some kind of obscene writing.
It must be pretty screwed-up
to go through all this trouble...
I'm sure this is the kind of ghost
Taketo would make if he died.
But the fact that we can't really
see it is the problem.
I guess there's no way to see a ghost.
Speaking of invisibility,
I once made a stealth suit.
What's that?
It makes you invisible,
but there were issues.
I sold it on the internet.
Could it be...
It's an evil spirit!
This evil presence,
wandering the dorm...
It must be an evil spirit!
We think so, as well.
I will purify and destroy it...
With all my power!
I-I can't take it!
If I were the Invisible Man,
this is the first thing I'd do.
If I open the door to this heaven...
No, no! I'm so close to a
new world of everyday eros...
Is this some trial, so
I grow as an author?
Isn't that underwear a bit flashy?
I decided to buy it anyway!
Who are you going to show it to?
That's a secret!
Everyday eros is good, but...
Normal eros is good, too!
I love it!
Hey, can't you feel
someone looking at us?
Th-This is bad. I can't get excited.
Calm down, libido!
Nope. Let's go take that bath.
N-No!
Shrivel up! Shrivel up already!
If they find me here...
N-No!
I've found you, slouching demon!
O-Oh, no!
Behold my dance that destroys evil!
Oh, mighty gods of purification,
take this great evil and sin,
and purify and destroy it!
Looks like it worked...
This dance will freeze solid
any kind of evil spirit.
Something's gotten solid.
I'll discover your true identity!
That's really bad!
If they find me here,
they'll destroy me...
I-I need to do something!
Give up!
I-I've got one chance...
I must fight her with everything I have!
Here I go!
Her purity made the Miko wish
to learn about the impure.
Wh-What?
And a pure body was the perfect prey
for his obscene desires!
No, Don't.
The Miko could no longer fight
the pleasure of having
body and soul tainted.
She was falling into lust.
I-I've failed...
I-I won.
How dare you hurt Mai?
I'll defeat you with my
holy powers, evil spirit!
Th-The suit is shorting out!
This is holy power.
I'll use my holy water to reveal
who you really are!
H-Holy water?
"It's time for confession!"
said the Sister, as
she raised her skirt!
The greater the taboo, the more the
woman within her screamed.
She wanted to give her body to a man,
not to God.
M-My holy power...
Her voice was no longer heard in Heaven,
as flames of desire burned her.
The only way to quench the flames
was with her own holy water.
Snap out of it!
I am still inexperienced.
F-Forgive me, oh Lord...
The slouching demon
is a terrifying foe...
I-I'm saved.
Sometimes, my own talent scares me.
Looks like you're still safe.
I'm not safe at all!
Things are getting really bad!
I think we have enough
now for a fine article.
It might be time to leave.
Permission to escape granted.
R-Roger!
The girl's dorm is at DEFCON 1.
We will now enter fortress mode.
People are too loud.
Wh-What do I do?
Good luck running!
I-I'm not even excited!
Oh, right. That suit...
The batteries are nearly dead.
It runs on batteries?!
If you avoid getting excited,
it'll last a bit longer.
No, no! That isn't the problem!
Reinforcements! I'm requesting
reinforcements!
Should you be caught or killed,
the Secretary will disavow any knowledge
of your actions. Bear that in mind.
This communicator will automatically
self-destruct in one second.
Ch-Chief!
H-Hey!
I've been abandoned!
The sensors aren't picking up anything.
I'm sure he's still in the dorm.
Your sensors can pick up ghosts?
Mine are special.
They'll capture any energy signal,
no matter how minor!
If he's inside, we just
need to smoke him out.
How?
If he's a perverted ghost,
then there's an easy way.
I see.
If I hide here...
Come on out, slouching ghost!
That's against the rules!
I-I can't look! If I get
excited, they'll see me...
My mind says one thing,
but my eyes aren't listening!
Bounce, bounce...
Over there! I found him.
Wah!
This way!
Ow!
He went that way!
Wait!
Wah!
You aren't getting away!
That way!
Wait!
Argh!
What has everyone so riled up?
Oh, Taketo?
I thought it was noisy around here.
So that was you?
You can see me?
I can tell without needing to see you.
How?
You're my photographic subject.
I'm always watching you, so I can tell.
You aren't going to turn me in to them?
I don't know what you did,
but do you want me to?
So, you can take photos like this, too?
Oh, that?
One guy and two girls.
A person can smile and laugh
until they show their true selves.
Did something happen?
But even after you show how
ugly you really are,
I guess you can still smile.
Lately, I've started to think that.
Someday, I might want to take
another photo like this.
Raika...
I use this escape route when I want to
leave the dorm to take photos.
I'll let you use it.
Th-Thanks.
Why are you helping me escape?
I'd be bored if you got expelled and I couldn't
take any more photos of you...
Get going, already.
Raika! Did you see a ghost?
Yeah, I did.
Where'd it go?
It ran.
We should seal this place,
so it never comes back.
Terror
Slouching
evil
spirit
Girls' dorm
secret report
marks left in the balcony
suddenly appeared in the dance studio
the sealed well!!
What is this article?!
People really like it.
They say it's a new seven mysteries
for the girls' dorms.
Blood dripping from thin air...
Words written in blood on a mirror.
And...
What happened to my report?!
It's there. In the left corner.
It was a wonderful place.
Special Report on
the Girls' Dorms!
Anonymous reporter.
That's all?
The thing with the ghost
was a much bigger deal.
If you're unhappy with it,
want to sneak in again?
I-I'm not going back there!
Jeez, you've gotta be kidding me...
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
Purify...
Yah!
Cleanse...
Preview:
"Holiday
Inspiration"
It's me, Enshuu Ritsu.
M-Math's just as good as anything else!
You can do...
a lot of things...
Like with triangles!
Or protractors!
All kinds of s-stuf—