You can't hide from me.
I can follow anywhere you go.
Call me "Onee-sama"!
Okay! I got myself a
super-platinum ticket to a classical concert!
Wow!
But we aren't at the point of
going on dates alone yet...
You know how to deal with that...
Just touch them, and that'll be that!
I can't do that.
Because I...
I haven't done anything.
Onee-sama?
Don't worry about it.
I only do that later.
Snack time!
Wake up!
This mark...
It's hers.
I'm not letting her
have my little sisters!
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Beyond Friends with Benefits"
So great... Just wonderful!
I can feel a masterpiece coming on.
I've settled on you.
U-Um...
Good morning, Fukune-chan.
I should have guessed you'd
talk to Fukune-chan.
Everyone's talking about
you, Botan-senpai.
You do have good taste...
You're quite famous yourself.
Everyone's talking about the silly
freshman whom her classmates call "Onee-sama."
Oh, are they?
So you knew that was my
little sister last night.
That's not your little sister anymore,
but one of my paintings.
I'll have to thank you properly.
I definitely will!
I'll look forward to it.
What has gotten into Ran this morning?
She's talking to Beni Botan-senpai.
Beni Botan?
I think I just heard that name
somewhere recently...
Taketo-san, have you heard of
the painted uniform incident?
Painted uniform incident?
A world-famous genius
of avant-garde art!
Th-That's Botan-senpai?
I've heard she'll make any motif
she likes into art, no matter what.
Into art...
I wish she'd see the difference between
being passionate and out of control.
Yeah.
She should come up with
a better use for that energy.
C-Come...
Not you too... People are watching...
We're in public.
Say it! Now! Loudly!
3.1415926...
Narukara-san is alone.
What are you staring at, ero-writer?
What?
It isn't your problem, is it?
First Botan-senpai, and now you...
Why does Fukune-chan attract
all these weirdos?
Wh-What? Botan-senpai? Seriously?
I won't let either of you touch her!
Not her... Not an ero-writer, like you!
Narukara Fukune-san, of class 1-3,
the Genius Cultural Activities Committee
is looking for you.
Please report to the teachers' office.
She's going...
The Genius Cultural
Activities Committee?
I've never heard of it before.
I'm sure some weirdo founded it.
This is Inspiration Academy, after all.
I knew it!
What?
The Prodigy Activities
and Business Committee
<Officer Introduction>
Ban
<Agamori
|
Beni Botan
Asaji
Rittou>
Beni Botan (Beni Botan)
Sengakuen High Class Academy, Third Year of Junior High.
Awarded at the twenty-ninth Worldwide Modern Art
Competition with special honors.
Aside from school, involved in many student-oriented
fine art activities.
Genius Cultural Activities Committee
Beni Botan
Beni Botan is president
of that committee...
She's set a trap for Fukune-chan!
I won't allow it!
Wait!
I'll go, too.
Why are you following me?
Because I'm worried about Narukara-san.
Imagining you're her knight in
shining armor or something?
Don't be ridiculous, ero-writer!
Th-That isn't important right now.
You don't think Fukune-chan would
want nothing to do with you?
I'll protect her myself.
Don't get in my way!
I...
It's coming... It's coming.
Um, what's this special event?
I already told you...
I plan to hold a big exhibition for all the
Inspiration Academy artistic geniuses.
So I need a really good,
new piece to be at its center.
You'll help me, right? Right?
But my practice...
Yes, I know.
But first, let me get started.
The world is empty, except for us.
No one can bother us.
Let's take our time and have fun...
I'm sorry, Onee-sama.
I couldn't find her.
It looks like her studio's
location is top-secret.
Just you wait, senpai!
Resistance is futile.
Expose everything to me.
Call me "Onee-sama"!
At that instant, forty-five
satellites were hacked,
including several military satellites
belonging to superpowers.
Simultaneously, all the school security cameras
fell under Musen Ran's control.
Inspiration Academy classrooms, check.
Girls' dorms, check.
Check.
Check...
Check!
I don't see her on any of the cameras...
Which means she's elsewhere!
I wonder what Botan-senpai's
doing right now...
Now it's your turn.
I can't waste time thinking about it!
I'd prefer you not use my spy cameras
for stuff like this.
Senpai! Don't try telling me you've forgotten
what you did to Fukune-chan.
If you don't stop complaining, you'll get
a big serving of the Musen Ran viruses
that took out the Department of Defense!
Right, right. I get it...
C-Clarinet...
Now, let's get started.
That's enough, Botan-senpai.
No way... How'd she find
my studio so easily?
Pretty clever...
Hiding your underground studio's entrance
in an abandoned incinerator.
It's a great hideout...
Perfect for having
some fun with someone.
What do you mean, fun?
You dragged her here, not even asking
what she thought about it.
She won't be having any fun at all!
Oh, my! Is that the problem?
Of course it is!
Gentle... Fun... And elegant.
That's how an onee-sama should be!
Then what if someone were
to take her tomorrow?
Would you be okay with that?
Wh-What?
The only thing I believe in is
the passion I feel, in the moment.
Truth exists solely in the present.
We're different. I don't try and excuse
the things of which I am bad.
Bad?!
That's right. I just said that you're bad
at dealing with girls...
Y-You're saying I'm bad with girls?
I'll never forgive you!
I see. Then you'll prove it?
And now...
An anything goes one-round match
to determine possession
of Narukara Fukune.
In the blue corner,
Class 3-2, Beni Botan!
In the red corner,
Class 1-3, Musen Ran!
I, Kiya Star, will provide commentary.
Genius Analyst
Mei Choushi
Analysis will be provided by the
genius analyst, Mei Choushi.
Hi, everyone.
I knew this would get crazy.
Ran starts by turning her back
on her opponent?
It'll be interesting to see what
happens here. Let's watch.
She smiled!
And she beckoned!
Making a younger sister uneasy,
by facing away in silence.
Then eliminating that discomfort,
by turning with a smile.
An onee-sama combo, relying on
a beckoning to double the joy.
All Ran's sisters have fallen over!
Quite effective.
Botan walks unsteadily toward her.
Will she go for a passionate embrace?
Or will she go ahead and steal a kiss?
Let's find out.
You caught me a little, but...
I prefer to do things more directly.
What's that? Are you shooting lasers
at me or something?
N-No...
A single glance is all it takes.
Ran, snap out of it!
Now, let's get started.
I told you, I like taking
the direct approach!
This is much faster.
Botan counterattacks
with a wild breast grab.
Ran's technique has been
completely countered!
This will be hard to escape.
Ran's technique relies heavily
on a set pattern...
A look, followed by a gesture,
followed by an embrace.
Botan's response is simply
to go after her physically.
Look! Botan starts running!
Why, you...
See? Do you understand now?
For all your talk of feelings,
ultimately, you just can't do it.
You feel good, don't you?
Even with me.
Now then, let's finish this.
There it is! Her
breast-painting technique!
Art and attack, all in one.
She really is a genius.
Ran!
Stupid, stupid, stupid. What are you doing?!
I guess that's the match.
What?!
Wh-What are you doing here?
No one asked you for help!
I know that!
But at this rate, Narukara-san will be turned
into one of her artworks, right?
Shut up!
This time,
I'll protect her.
Ran, I have an idea.
As a porno writer, I'm
very aroused by her.
I'll hit her with all that libido.
It should give you an opening, at least.
Will you let me help
you? Just this once...
To protect Narukara-san.
B-But...
I...
Ran!
Oh, my! Botan has dragged
Narukara-san into the ring,
not waiting for the match to end!
Now, let's begin.
Narukara-san is waiting.
Don't screw this up, or else!
Same to you.
C-Clarinet...
That's far enough.
Oh, you're still standing?
But I doubt you can do anything,
with your body in that state.
Ran returned!
Could the match not be decided?
See? I knew it.
Ran is down!
Is she finally out?
Hey! Uh...
That's right. The match is over.
But an artist could never
be satisfied by this alone.
Only the finest canvas could show off
the image nurtured within her mind.
The finest canvas?
That's you!
Yes, the artist's own body!
I...
...am the canvas?
First, she tasted the
ripe, swelling oranges.
Her body hardened at the thought
of glistening strawberries,
plucked by their tips.
A heart-shaped peach...
And at the center of this fruit,
a spring of hot, flowing turpentine.
She draws.
And she is drawn on...
An eternal Ouroboros of creation.
Giving herself over, to a state of ecstasy
she had never before known,
the artist forgot all else.
More! More...
Now, Ran!
No!
I'll show you!
An onee-sama...
Gazes into your eyes.
Takes your hand.
H-Her attack...
Lends you her shoulder.
I-I can't stop!
Looks into your heart...
And in the end,
does this!
There it is! The genius programmer
Ran is showing her true power...
A speedy rain of gentle caresses!
It's... It's good.
Call me "Onee-sama"!
It isn't that I can't do it.
I just don't go as far
as I can, senpai.
She's down!
Botan has lost the match!
Ran pretended to go down splendidly,
and Botan lowered her guard.
No, Botan would have normally
seen through that feint.
Had she not been utterly
entranced by that reading...
I-I did it...
Are you okay? Does it hurt anywhere?
Wh-Where's Botan-senpai?
Forget about her.
She'll be preoccupied
for a while, I'm sure!
Musen-san, did you save me?
Thank y—
Hey, Fukune-chan...
My head is spinning.
That was a really thick nosebleed...
Um...
N-N-Nar... Narukara-san?
Why?
Um, Musen-san told me
that it was really Akutagawa-kun
who protected me.
So I came here...
Ran told you that?
She wanted me to give you this, too.
Don't get the wrong idea.
An onee-sama is always fair.
That's the only reason.
P.S.
You're still scum and an ero-writer,
but I guess you might be
right for Fukune-chan...
If not for me, and maybe
three or four others.
Ran...
Um...
Y-Yeah?
Thank you.
Aw, it was nothing...
Why are you always helping me?
I-I like hearing your clarinet!
Like...
You practice every day, right?
Let's both do our best, okay? Bye!
Like...
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
From the front...
From behind...
Preview:
"What If
Inspiration Academy's
Genius Manager..."
Preview:
"What If
Inspiration Academy's
Genius Manager..."
It's time for a Musen Ran riddle!
What's sweet and soft,
and touching them makes girls
cry out, in cute, happy voices?
You all know the answer.
Too bad! It's bo—