Inspiration
Futarikiri paradise
ふたりきりパラダイス
A paradise all to ourselves...
I love you
I love you!
aishite ageru Summer Days
恋してあげる Summer Days
I love you, summer days!
Matteta kiss ni komete
待ってた kiss にこめて
I've been waiting for this kiss,
Hashiridashita
走り出した
and I start to run.
natsuiro memories
夏色 memories
Summer-colored memories!
Thanks, everyone!
And that was the 1-B presentation,
a Sonokoe Utae special hot springs concert!
Let's see what the judges thought!
Inspiration Festival Ground
Right now, 1-2 is in the lead with all the points!
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Steamy Town Elegy"
To understand what's happening at Inspiration Academy,
we go back one week.
This is the best!
I feel so relaxed...
It's hard to believe we're at school.
Yes. We're on Inspiration Academy grounds.
Genius Inn
Manager
The geniuses who found a hot spring
on campus came together,
Genius
Dowser
Digger
Genius
Genius Hot
Springs
Manager
Genius Hot
Springs
Manager
to build a gigantic town
centered on the hot springs.
This feels great.
I wish there were more places like this...
Leave that to me.
I'll excavate a bunch more!
Good luck!
Let's start over there.
Hey!
Are you trying to dig a hole in the bathtub?
You can't just randomly dig,
expecting to find a hot spring!
You can't?
Ill-omened...
I can't see...
This is disgusting, Taketo!
I guess everyone does it.
If you want so much to see
someone naked, I'll...
If you want to see, stop hiding and look!
Taketo-kun...
U-Utae-san... I, well...
You've got guts, breaking into the girls' bath!
Are you following your
overwhelming passion? How ugly!
No!
Someone just knocked us into the wall!
Who might that be?
Me!
10/10!
Tetsubou Meguru
Genius
Gymnast!!
First years...
Haven't you been slacking off a bit lately?
Botan-senpai?
Did you attend this school just to
screw around at a hot spring?
Losers.
You think you can come here
and boss us around?
The only one who's screwed-up and
screwing around is Taketo!
You're blaming this on me?
You really are loafing about.
You're worthless... A waste of genius.
Are we really that bad?
As upperclassmen, we can't ignore this.
We need to teach you a lesson.
We'll administer a test, to see if you're
truly worthy of Inspiration Academy.
A test? What kind of test?
We're holding an orientation tournament
for all the first-year classes!
A tournament for all the classes?
The Inspiration Hot Springs Town
will host the first round.
Giving us an event that only
a genius could create.
The second and third year
students will judge you.
And the number one class...
...wins!
Taketo-kun...
Inspiration Hot
Springs Town
This place is completely deserted...
I just can't believe people don't
see how great this is!
Mathematics                Fortune Telling
Mathematics Fortune Telling is kinda lame.
How rude!
It's a revolutionary type of fortune telling,
based on my theory of the similarities between naughty milk bottles and lone left socks,
all combined with the theory of relativity.
I don't understand any of that!
We're done for...
A concert by the world's most popular idol...
Completely unfair!
I thought outdoor shops,
in a hot springs town,
are such fixtures, they'd have to be popular.
Bug Battle Arena
Habanero Drinks
Cutting
Cabbage
Ten
Straight
Hours!
It sucks, but I guess no one
can match Utae-san's charms...
Ah, except Narukara-san!
And the rest of us can't?
We just have to win from here on.
Let's both do our best, okay?
I have to hold a concert...
A concert?
That's right! We could do that!
If they're having a concert, then we should
have Fukune-chan hold one, too!
I see. An eye for an eye, huh?
I have a solo concert at the National Music Hall!
Th-The National...
A concert?
That's amazing!
Only people who are recognized
as the best play there.
A stage for the chosen ones only, right?
That's only natural. Your music's the best!
I wanted to refuse, but...
It's fine. If that's how it is, then it's okay.
That's right! Good luck, Narukara.
U-Um...
Don't worry. We'll be all right.
Taketo will think of some way around this.
I will?!
You do want to let Fukune-chan
focus on her performance, right?
Don't mess it up!
I wanted to go and cheer her on...
I'm sorry I can't go. But let everyone else
hear your wonderful music, okay?
Good luck.
Class 1-A tried an all-male, BL play.
Romeo-kun and Juliet-kun
But it was only popular with a
small set of devoted female fans.
Romeo-kun and Juliet-kun
Without the score they hoped for,
they ended up losing.
Inspiration
Festival Ground
Will class 3 be able to overtake
class 2's heavy lead?
How pathetic...
I'm surprised you call yourselves geniuses,
with that level of skill.
You average people!
If you don't like that, then show us your talent.
It's gonna be hard to come back from this.
But I told Narukara-san to do her best,
so I can't give up now...
Taketo-kun...
Utae-san? You're still wearing your outfit?
I was told to keep wearing it
through the first round.
Don't stare at me...
I'm sorry!
I guess class 2 relied on you for everything.
That'll be hard to beat...
I'm sorry. I feel like it's my fault.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
I wasn't happy about how it would affect you.
But the rest of the class insisted.
It's a tournament, so it makes sense.
I wish I were in your class, Taketo-kun.
Oh, well. Come on and play!
I bet you haven't netted goldfish in a long time!
Yeah! I loved it when I was a kid.
Here you go!
Thanks!
Which should I go for?
I like the red ones, but the
pop-eyed ones are nice, too...
Okay, I'll go for the pop-eyed ones!
Those bulges on her chest,
seen when I was young...
The summer day we first recognized
each other as man and woman,
beginning to climb the stairs to adulthood.
And the boy became a man...
He stood up, bold and strong!
That's pretty good!
Pretty good...
Um, well...
Did you get an idea for a novel?
Naughty.
There's no sound.
Good luck, good luck, Utae-san!
I was so close...
Don't worry about it.
Why are you playing around?
You have an idea on how
we can get out of this, right?
I can't just come up with something like that.
So you went on a date with the enemy?
You must think we're all idiots.
Don't call her the enemy...
Utae-san is my friend!
Friend?
Just think of something, already.
But Narukara-san isn't here.
If she were, I bet I could
come up with something...
Let me help.
I'll do anything I can to help!
You're from class 2, though.
I-I am, but...
I want to help Taketo-kun. Okay?
The classes are competing. You can't do that.
Yeah...
I'm glad you'd want to help, but...
I may be an idol, but I'm still a girl!
I always have lots of fans who cheer me on.
But as a girl, sometimes I'd like
to cheer someone on.
Utae-san...
Thank you!
I'm so happy you said that!
That's it!
Yes?
Dad?
Girl Genius
Narukara
Fukune
Solo Concert
Aim carefully!
You're aiming for the pink nipples!
I did it.
He got the areola!
Hey, Ran. The words...
N-No... Not there!
I'm sick of saying this stuff!
You want the customers to leave?
O-Oh, fine!
Oh, you're such a pervert, aiming there!
Let's keep at it!
All right!
Perfect shot! Strike!
That's it!
I love it when you touch me there!
Now, if you think these are normal
water yo-yo's, you're in for a big surprise.
Look carefully...
There's a really ero-ero one in there.
Yo-yo fishing, one of the
world's strangest hobbies!
Don't screw up and hook the bikinis.
Of course, everyone messes up sometimes...
He was aiming for the bikini the whole time!
No!  This bikini hooks in the front!
Hey, the yo-yo's aren't allowed to run...
Just lie there!
Ugly.
This is your strategy?
Eros is humanity's most basic instinct.
Aim toward it, and people will flock to you.
I agree with you that people are basically ugly.
No one can resist the lure of eros.
We're sure to win now!
Pink Butt Candy Apples
Maybe I'll switch to class 3...
Eros Chocolate
ABananas
A guy would be happiest in class 3!
Okay, that's it...
Everyone's having a great time.
I was surprised.
Yeah, now it'll be a close match.
I'm impressed, Taketo-kun.
It's all thanks to you, Utae-san.
Thank you so much!
I'm excited, just knowing it's the musical genius, Master Narukara's daughter.
I've heard it's like the sound of an angel.
Daddy!
Music chooses you.
Those whom the music chooses
are called "geniuses."
I love your music!
My music...
What is my music?
Sonokoe Utae Autograph and Handshake Event
Why aren't more people here?
Looks like they're all over there, with class 3.
I'm so humiliated, having all my customers
stolen by those filthy shops!
It can't be helped.
It's a competition.
You're not upset?
They're doing their best, too.
It's more fun to have rivals.
So that's how it works?
Except in love...
Good luck, good luck!
Good luck! Aim well!
Shoot well, and hear the very voice of Eros!
So keep firing, to keep her talking!
Thank you for your support!
Sonokoe Utae Autograph and Handshake Event
I love you, Utae-chan.
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you, Utae-san.
Thank you so much!
Good luck, Utae-chan!
Thank you...
And the first round of the orientation
tournament came to a close.
Damn it! We were so close...
We almost won...
It's unfortunate, but we did our best.
The winner of round one
is class 1-2!
We were really surprised by class 3.
I was impressed that you managed
to mount such a comeback.
It was a pretty interesting match...
But we're just getting started.
It's a three-round match!
What?
The second round measures who
raises the most money...
And the third round is a chorus.
Class 2 won this round, so they get 100 points.
Class 3 came in second, so they get 50 points.
Naturally, last place gains no points.
The class with the most points,
at the end of all the matches, wins.
And the triumphant class will win
an ultra luxurious vacation!
You can go anywhere you want on Earth.
Everyone, want to go on a trip?
A final choral competition?
Class 2 has Utae-chan, so they
maintain the advantage...
That's not true.
When Narukara-san returns,
we can ask her to accompany us.
That's right!
This time, we can do more
than simply match them!
Taketo-kun, nice work today.
Congratulations on your victory, Utae-san!
It was close.
You were amazing.
I'm really tired now, though.
I feel like spending some time in a hot spring.
And where are we right now?
This is wonderful...
Utae-san!
I came.
Y-You came?
No one was on the other side.
I don't have many chances to visit a hot spring,
and I'd be lonely by myself...
So, may I come in?
Um, well I guess. But...
G-Go ahead!
Thank you.
I'm sorry...
It's kind of strange...
Getting in a bath with you alone, Taketo-kun.
Y-Yeah.
I guess I might be a little embarrassed,
sharing a bath with a guy.
I-I bet! I mean I'm embarrassed, too!
Even though you're a porno author?
Fantasy and reality are different.
I've never seen a naked girl!
What?
Nothing!
Oh, right. Sorry for making you help me investigate the chief.
I almost caused you to freeze to death.
No, it was really fun!
Really?
Because I was with you.
I don't think I've been that excited
since my debut concert.
I'd really like to do something
like that with you again.
M-M-Man, it's really gotten dark!
Come to think of it, I wonder how it went.
How what went?
Narukara-san's concert today.
I wanted to go and cheer her on.
But I'm sure she was fine on her own, right?
Hey, by the way...
The last round is a chorus, right?
I've always sung alone,
so I'm really looking forward
to singing with everyone!
Me, too.
I'm going to ask Narukara-san
to accompany us.
Don't you think that'd be a good match?
That's true.
But it will be kind of hard...
Remember what Botan-senpai said?
By the way, for the last round,
we'll have you sing an original song.
Writing the lyrics and music will
be critical, so good luck!
The girls want me to write the lyrics...
Words are your specialty!
But I can only write porn.
But that's your talent, right?
True, but...
I don't want her to know
that I'm a porno author...
You mean Fukune-san?
Yeah.
Why not?
Why not? I wonder. I guess, I just don't.
Not many girls like porno, you know.
It'd be one thing if I were a normal author.
I see. So that's how he feels
about Fukune-san...
I like it.
Thanks. You're one of the few who
understands me, aren't you?
That's why I can tell you anything.
Sorry.
But Fukune-san's different, isn't she?
Fukune-san would understand!
You just need to really try
and come up with lyrics...
Even if they're a bit naughty,
I'm sure you can write a wonderful song!
Y-Y-You really think so?
Of course!
Your lyrics and Fukune-san's accompaniment...
It will produce a wonderful harmony!
Okay?
Yeah... Somehow, your saying that
made me feel a lot better!
I'm glad.
Inspiration Hot
Springs Town
It seems you're still unable to understand.
Did you forget?
I'm not the one you should be learning about.
Ch-Chief?
You need to realize before it's too late...
Karaoke House
wakatteru watshi janakute
shisen no anokogairuwa
I know it isn't me you're looking at. It's her...
Teardrop Clover
Whom did she mean?
The person I need to learn about...
Narukara-san?
Welcome back. How was the concert?
We lost, but...
But we came in really close!
Even Botan-senpai was surprised
by how well we did.
I wish you could've seen it!
Anyway, the last round is a chorus.
I'd like you to play the accompaniment!
If you play your clarinet,
the song will be wonderful.
I think we'd win for sure!
So...
N-Narukara-san?
Narukara-san...
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
I took it off. Everything I have...
It's all for you!
Preview:
"Our Summertime Blue"
It's me, Sonokoe Utae.
Sh... No.
Don't make any noise, or they'll hear us.
So, be quiet and soft.
Okay?
No! No...
Don't move so much!
You can—