It's morning, huh?
It was a long night...
N-Narukara-san?
She ended up coming back to my room.
And she hasn't said a word since then.
Was she really tired? She just fell asleep...
What happened?
Y-You'll catch a cold...
I'm sorry.
Father...
Morning, Taketo! Are you still asleep?
Fine, then...
I'm in a hurry. I'll have to leave without you.
Good morning.
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Our Summertime Blue"
It's really great,
this song Iikyoku Kanade-san wrote.
Something's missing.
Iikyoku
Kanade
Songwriter
Genius
Y-You're right. The lyrics aren't done yet.
But are you sure about this?
Having Akutagawa-kun write the lyrics?
He's the only one with any kind of
writing talent in our class.
Even if he is a genius porno author...
With Narukara-san's accompaniment,
we're sure to win the chorus competition.
But where are they?
You hugged me, out of the blue...
What happened, Narukara-san?
I have to ask.
I don't understand...
Lunch break, huh?
I've never skipped school in my life.
Me, neither.
I've never stayed home from school...
without telling anyone.
I shouldn't be smiling now! Stupid!
Our next item is Utae-chan's favorite bear!
She's used this bear for a lot,
and any fan would want it.
Let's start at 5,000 yen!
This goes over here, and that goes over there...
Helping to run things might be harder than
actually participating in the orientation!
120,000 yen!
120,000 yen! Is that the high bid?
125,000 yen!
Things are really heating up...
133,000!
Utae-chan?
Class 2 is using Utae-chan for the
money-making round, huh?
We're doing fine, too.
We have the genius programmer and
the genius mathematician teaming up!
A-About that...
What happened to those two?
Ritsu's complicated
economic-forecasting formula,
and Ran's program, which instantly
responds to worldwide conditions.
Working together, they became
overnight millionaires!
We did it!
Did you guys convert that to cash?
The round two rules stated to raise cash.
Computer data...
...doesn't count.
In the second round,
class 1-2 wins, with 200 points.
Class 1-1 gets 100 points.
Coming in third,
1-3 receives nothing!
My theory was perfect.
But... But...
Our only hope now is to stage a
comeback in the chorus battle!
I don't like having that
ero-idiot writing the lyrics...
But with Fukune-chan's clarinet, we'll be fine!
Right, Fukune-chan?
Aw, don't worry about it...
No.
You made coffee for me, so at least let me make you lunch.
Wait just a little longer.
This is great... It's like we're newlyweds.
No, like a couple that's just started dating!
No, no!
No, I need to ask what happened...
What's this smell?
It's burning!
Are you sad?
No... It's so good, I'm crying.
That's great!
I've never made these before.
I'll make them again, okay?
S-Some other time, sure...
Hey, isn't it almost time for practice?
You can do it here if you want.
No, that's all right.
Narukara-san?
Oh, right. I mentioned this a little yesterday...
But for the orientation tournament
chorus battle,
would you play your clarinet for us?
W-We're sure to win if you'll help us!
But first, I have to write the lyrics...
Lyrics?
You're writing them?
Y-Yeah.
Everyone asked me to.
What kind? What kind of lyrics are you writing?
What kind...
Well...
But I can only write porn.
Fukune-san would understand!
U-U-Uh...
Uh, about eternal love...
How you can't abandon your dreams!
Or the treasure of friendship!
Maybe something like that...
That's amazing.
You really are a genius...
You're totally different than me.
Narukara-san?
That's not true.
You have something you care about.
See?
Akutagawa-kun...
I...
You're far more amazing than I am.
You're a genius!
So don't look like that...
Everyone's counting on your clarinet.
No...
Narukara-san?
I'm not a genius.
I can't do it...
The music didn't choose me.
I'm not a genius...
I'm not a genius at all!
Not even with the clarinet...
I've never enjoyed it or thought it was fun!
I hate everything about it!
Fukune-san?
Narukara Fukune Withdraws
from Inspiration Academy?
What is this?
Fukune Narukara-san,
clarinet genius from 1-3,
has asked to withdraw from
Inspiration Academy.
This decision appears to be
motivated by her father,
Narukara Fukuzoushi, one of
the world's greatest clarinet players.
Narukara-san's going to a different school.
That's way bigger than this chorus thing...
Taketo?
NEWSPAPER
CIRCLE
Is that article true?
It's just a rumor, but yes.
But as a genius, it may be better
that she studies across the world.
Better for her?
Don't say mean things like that!
Please...
Mean, huh?
Then, did you know about this?
Yesterday, Narukara-san's solo concert
was a huge disaster.
Halfway through the performance,
she stopped being able
to play, for some reason.
The staff didn't know what else to do,
except lower the curtain.
And then, she didn't return
to her dorm afterward.
She went and hid somewhere.
She probably felt so terrible,
she just wanted someone
to make her feel better...
Fukune-chan!
It's not true, is it?
You're not leaving, right?
Right? Right?!
Fukune-chan!
No response, huh?
Then I'll force my way in!
Come on, Ran... Calm down!
But why did this happen, all of a sudden?
Why? No one's seen her
since the concert ended.
I didn't see Akutagawa-kun yesterday, either.
Taketo?
If I'd known what was going on
with Narukara-san...
If you'd known what was going on?
What happened to her?
She was in your room?!
When she was feeling her worst,
she chose you, not me.
Fukune-chan...
Ran...
However,
I can't believe she'd leave the school.
That she'd just disappear.
I can't believe it!
Why? Why did this happen?
What should we do?
I don't know what's happening anymore!
I'm going to write those lyrics.
What are you talking about?
This isn't the time to worry about that.
That's why.
There's no way that Narukara-san hates music.
Or hates her clarinet.
She might be closing off her heart right now.
But music is the only way to open it.
We'll have to bet everything on our chorus!
I'll show her who I really am...
I'll write porno lyrics!
You may be right.
I hate to admit it, but with your porno talents,
you might write something incredible.
I'm going to tell Narukara-san...
With my lyrics, I'll tell her how I...
I mean, how we feel!
Taketo!
What are you two doing in there without me?
We're getting started. All of us.
Before that...
Hang on to this.
O-Okay...
That's the price for holding her clarinet.
But without lyrics or accompaniment,
isn't victory impossible?
A genius doesn't acknowledge the impossible!
Losing doesn't bother you?
I guess we have no choice.
At this rate, we can't call ourselves geniuses.
Yeah.
I'm going to write them!
With the passion I put into
my pornographic novels,
I'll write lyrics that stand up
proud, strong, and erect!
I can't write...
You're a genius, right?
How can writing lyrics scare you?
Or can you not be a lyricist?
No, that's impossible!
But if it were a pornographic novel...
Awaken...
To new heights, to new pleasures...
To overflowing passion!
Please tell me...
I want you to use your talents
to show me what love truly is.
I want you to fill me up with your emotion.
Fill me up...
I can feel it! It's overflowing!
I can write them...
Narukara-san.
Just wait, Narukara-san.
I'm writing this for you.
What kind of lyrics are you writing?
You really are a genius, Akutagawa-kun.
You're totally different than Fukune.
What are you writing?
I heard Akutagawa-kun writes porno novels!
Oh, man. How creepy...
We'd better stay away from him.
It's not like that! Pornography is an art, and...
And I'm telling stories about love!
I hate you.
What am I doing?
Inspiration Academy
Newspaper Circle
If it were me,
I could be with you forever...
Taketo-kun.
Akutagawa Taketo-kun
Yeah... Somehow, your saying that
made me feel a lot better!
Inspiration Academy
Newspaper Circle
I'm becoming a horrible person.
Go! Go! Utae!
You can do it! You can do it, Utae!
Fight! Fight! Utae!
Ow...
What are you doing, Katsuyo-san?
What else?
I'm cheering you on.
Me?
You looked like you were lonely, worrying a lot.
So I came to cheer for you!
Whatever happens, you should be
honest about your feelings.
That's for the best!
Go! Go! Utae!
Fight! You can do it! Let's go!
Cheer up, Utae-chan!
Knock those tears out of the park!
As I thought... School wasn't
something you needed.
Father...
You must be a genius at all times,
in all conditions.
That is what your clarinet demands.
That is why you exist.
I love your music!
"Love will never lose."
"Do your best, and hope will find you."
"Don't give up."
"Your dream will come true."
"I am always by your side."
I could write all kinds of lyrics like those.
That would...
I hate you.
It would keep her from hating me any more than she does now.
I like that face.
That's what I'm looking for in a photo.
Raika.
The ultimate ugliness...
A man who abandons himself,
to run from everything.
Well? Ugly, right?
I...
I don't have a choice!
Do you know what the
ugliest thing in the world is?
A liar.
A liar...
One who talks about opening a person's heart,
but seals off their own.
One who claims to want to save someone,
but only talks about what's convenient.
And in the end,
excuses are all they have.
I like that face. It's wonderful.
An ugliness worthy of the title, "Liar."
No.
This isn't me.
The real me...
I'm not like that!
I guess I failed as a cameraman,
becoming so involved with a subject.
I'm horrible.
So, I really am the ugliest of them all...
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
Cute?
Sexy?
Which do you like?
Preview:
"I Love You!!"
This is Akutagawa Taketo.
Actually, I..
I'm a girl!
My mom and sister entered
something I wrote
into a contest without asking me.
And actually, I hate writing
about boobs and butts...
I don't like it at all!
Wh-What are you doing, Onee-chan?