I love your music!
Would
it really
be
okay to
accept...
Would it really be okay to accept
his burning manhood?
Before she could reach an answer,
her body grew moist...
That's no good.
N-No good?
Is this the end for the Newspaper Circle?
Is my writing really that bad?
Circulation's dropped drastically?
No.
Th-Then the school isn't letting us publish?
Even I thought that last article
was kind of pushing it...
That's not it.
If the Newspaper Circle's done for,
I'll have nothing left to live for.
I'll have to disappear.
What was that?
Who knows? The chief's full of mysteries.
Now that I think of it, I don't know
anything about the chief.
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Director of X-Files"
Please, Ran...
Just her name or address.
Go ask the chief yourself.
If she'd tell me, I wouldn't have to ask you.
Ah, well. I guess I do owe you one.
You want me to search the
academy database, right?
Search
-
Newspaper Circle Chief
Next
Back
No       Hits
-
Newspaper Circle Chief
No       Hits
Search
No data found matching your request.
Next
Back
Close
I guess we need her name...
Or we could simply search for her by picture.
This is the facial recognition system
used by the FBI.
I'll find any photos of her,
in or out of the school.
Wow, I didn't know you could do that.
Oh? You think some firewall will stop me?
You're really well protected, aren't you?
Too bad! You can't hide anything from me.
R-Ran!
How naughty you are. Show me everything,
and I'll make you feel better!
That's right... You're my slave now.
Call me Onee-sama!
You did it! Way to go, Ran!
That's strange... This graduation
photo is two years old.
Two years old?
This class trip took place twenty years ago.
Wh-What does it mean?
This is over a hundred years old.
I've got photos of her from every era.
Who is the chief, really?
It's kind of creepy. Wouldn't it be best
not to get more deeply involved?
I don't have a choice.
It's going to bug me so much,
I won't be able to write!
I will solve this mystery!
She disappeared? No way!
Is she a ghost?!
In this form, I can't satisfy you, can I?
You still have those wonderful breasts.
They're more than enough.
That's disgusting.
There are things in this world
that must remain un— No!
Disgusting!
It was just a gust of wind...
Oh, it's you, Taketo. Don't scare me like that.
She has legs.
I'm glad to see you taking an
interest in your work, but...
What the hell were you thinking?
The chief is a ghost? Are you an idiot?
Have your blue balls finally driven you crazy?
It's possible, right?
There are pictures of ghosts.
Th-Those are just photographic errors.
But...
I said it's impossible! Totally impossible!
Might you be scared of ghosts?
Th-That's not true!
Then help me.
I-I refuse!
Only ugly photographs interest me.
I guess she really is frightened.
It doesn't matter. If I keep
following her, eventually...
Oh, fine.
Knock a home run out of the park!
Too bad, stranded on base. Don't mind, girl!
How long will she be in there?
I haven't taken my eyes off the entrance,
so I'm sure she's still inside.
Is she sick? Or...
What are you doing?
U-Utae-san!
Peeking?
N-N-N-No!
I'm just kidding... I know that's not it.
Hey, Utae-san.
Could you see if the chief's in there?
Sure, I guess.
Chief, you in there?
Newspaper Circle Chief-san?
That ought to do it.
Looks like she isn't in there.
N-No way!
Chief! You're in there, right? Come out!
They came out...
L-Little delinquent!
That really is a strange story.
I can't believe she just disappeared.
That toilet's on the 4th floor, so she
couldn't have used the window.
It doesn't make sense...
Maybe I should just give up...
I'm not a detective. I'm just a porno author.
Maybe I'm not cut out for this.
I'll help you!
In mysteries, all great detectives
have a partner, right?
Let's solve the mystery together, Holmes!
Utae-san...
This time, it's my turn to help you.
I don't see anything strange.
B-Be careful.
It's fine.
If anything happens, let me know immediately.
Sorry. You can't see at all from there, can you?
No, I can see just fine...
No! It's nothing!
T-Taketo-kun, are you okay?
I think I'm dying...
I'm so happy, I'm dying...
If we find her house, I'm sure
we'll solve the mystery.
But aren't these outfits a bit much?
I've worn outfits like this on TV.
They really make you feel
like a detective, right?
You're totally into this, aren't you, Utae-san?
Huh? Well...
C-Come on! We have to follow her.
What is she doing?
Oh, no!
Utae-san!
We'll pretend we're boyfriend and girlfriend.
It happens all the time in movies, right?
I said we were pretending.
Of course. We're pretending to be in love.
No!
Not in public...
If you struggle, she'll notice us.
We're lovers right now, aren't we?
You're so mean...
Taketo-kun!
The chief disappeared!
She was just there a second ago!
We only looked away for a second.
L-Let's look for her! I'll take the main building.
You check the girl's dorms.
N-Narukara-san...
G-Good evening.
Th-Thanks for earlier. Heading home?
Y-Yeah!
U-Uh, bye...
U-Um...
S-Sorry!
How's it going there?
She isn't there? I don't see her, either.
Fine. I'll come and meet you right now.
Sorry, what were you saying?
No, it was nothing.
We lost her today, but let's try again tomorrow.
Yeah. That's right.
No, I've never talked to a boy like this before.
I guess it makes me kind of nervous...
I like it.
A mystery circle?
That's where she was yesterday,
when she lifted her arms up to the sky.
The chief's involved somehow?
Do you think she's an alien?
No way.
It's a real possibility.
I searched for records related to
those photographs of the chief.
UFOs were spotted in the same locations,
about 40% of the time.
Then the chief is...
The chief is an alien.
But it's only 40%, right?
That's a pretty high probability.
Ritsu...
If two records match with that probability,
it's no coincidence.
Looks like you're sneaking around
for some reason.
Just the two of you...
Y-You've got it all wrong!
She's just helping me. Right?
Y-Yeah.
Forget that! What about the chief?
We're in big trouble if aliens
are infiltrating the school.
But aliens? Seriously?
Some mathematical equations prove the
existence of extraterrestrial life.
According to Drake's equation...
H-Hey, we can't come to that conclusion yet.
We aren't sure about this!
C-Come?
T-Taketo...
Th-The formula, Ritsu!
3.14159...
So, what do we do?
We have to find evidence...
Something that proves she's an alien!
I see. I understand.
If the chief's an alien, why would
she come to this school?
Why?
The Earthlings' energy, overflowing with life...
It's all mine.
Her tongue's going so deep...
Please take it all!
It might be worth it...
Nothing!
I'll log into CIA and former-KGB databases
for all the information I need!
N-No way! How?
And then it went boom! Then ka-boom!
And then kra-koom!
This is Snake. SitRep. Over.
All green. The chief hasn't
noticed anything. Over.
Good. Let's get a little closer.
U-Um, did you need something?
Yeah, I guess so...
Run!
They're going to catch us!
I'll protect Taketo!
We're safe...
I'm sorry this happened to you.
No, I'm fine.
Detectives get in this kind of
trouble all the time, right?
But...
Come on, partner. Keep your spirits up!
I'm really happy to be able to
help you out like this, Taketo-kun.
So, no apologies.
Utae-san...
I couldn't get any data...
Someone messed with the power!
Someone?
It has to be the chief's men!
Does that mean she doesn't
want us to investigate?
Most likely. I think we should stop.
But...
You could end up in even more
danger next time, Utae-chan!
You shouldn't get involved in stuff like this!
Is that so? Understood.
Ran might be right.
Taketo-kun...
This is it then?
Hey, why do you want to know
the chief's true identity?
Well, you know...
There's a trust between a writer and an editor.
I think you shouldn't have any doubts
about the person you're working with.
I guess that's why.
Then you mustn't give up!
To write good novels, you need her. Right?
So you can't give up!
Utae-san...
Let's both do our best, okay?
Then may I ask you something?
Why are you doing all this for me?
W-Well...
I think that I...
I think maybe it's because I like you!
I'm a fan of Akutagawa Taketo, the author.
What is she doing here?
This isn't somewhere she has any reason to be.
Maybe there's a secret UFO base here.
In the school?
But this building...
Music Room 3
Taketo-kun, the chief...
No!
We only took our eyes off of her for a second.
She must've gone inside.
N-Narukara-san?
Akutagawa-kun! You came to see me!
Taketo-kun?
Fukune-san?
The chief isn't here, is she?
No.
Narukara-san, sorry to interrupt your practice.
Fine...
Isn't that the loading dock where they
bring in teaching supplies?
Yeah, I think so.
What do we do?
Let's go.
It's cold...
What is this place?
A freezer?!
O-Oh, no!
I-It's not opening...
No...
How did this happen?
Th-The chief isn't here.
Damn it... I have to do something!
If there's an air duct somewhere...
I see light!
What is this?
Utae-san!
I'm so sleepy...
Y-You can't fall asleep here!
I'm fine...
What should I do? I never thought we
could freeze to death at school.
I must ensure that Utae-san survives at least.
There's one thing they always do
when stranded on a mountain.
Strip and keep each other warm.
It's the only way.
No, no! This isn't the time for that...
Wake up, Utae-san!
There's something I'd like
to say, no matter what.
If this is the end...
Don't say this is the end!
If I fall asleep now, I know I'd regret it.
You see, I...
I... Taketo-kun, I...
Utae-san?
Taketo-kun...
Good...
You were about to freeze to death.
You saved us, chief?
Yes.
Th-Thank you.
There are some things in this world
you should leave alone.
Oh, right. The Newspaper Circle will
continue to function normally.
I'm counting on you for more articles.
Wait, chief!
I'm not the one you should be learning about.
Why?
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
Come have some of my dumplings...
Preview:
"Steamy Town
Elegy"
It's me, the chief.
What do I like?
What else?
Long ones, hard ones...
Sometimes, I love sucking on them outside.
I never tire of—