Misao! Misao!
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
I'm sure you were enjoying some
perverted imaginary performance.
You're a real ape,
a horny ape that'll
chase anything he sees.
Wh-Why are you photographing me?
"An Idol, Even if I Strip!"
Aren't you here to photograph her?
Raika was right.
I was totally under her spell.
Utae! Utae!
Utae!
No, I'm not the only one.
The whole world cheers for her now.
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
Here.
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
New First-Years Featured Report!
Take notice of this First-year!
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
Second
Section               "Idol Singer Genius"
Sonokoe            Utae
She ranked first, in our reader's choice survey,
for potential interview subjects.
Make sure you don't mess up this time.
Because if you do...
If I do?
You want to know the details?
I-I'll do my very best.
Sonokoe Utae.
Even Ran's here?
No, I guess it isn't that strange.
Because Ran's...
N-Narukara-san?
Just forget it. I have
to do the interview.
No!
My Tsukuru-Style stage
props are the best.
That explosion was even bigger
than I anticipated!
So what did you think, Fukune-chan?
What? You didn't see them?
I don't know.
I see.
Then, let's go get some ice cream.
Excuse me.
W-Wonderful!
Good morning.
No, u-um... I-I'm Ak... A-Ak...
Akutagawa Taketo-kun, right?
I'm Sonokoe Utae. Nice to meet you.
You know me?
Of course! The genius
high-school novelist.
Yes... I suppose so, but...
What do you write?
Gulp!
Everything always goes
well up to this part.
This is where everything falls apart...
No! Pervert!
Y-You've got it all wrong!
I'm used to it.
But I really don't want
her to hate me, too.
Porno.
Bu... Wha...?
Por...no?
And we're done.
Now comes the slapping,
the kicking, and the running...
Wow!
I always thought pornographic novels
were written by scary people.
Um, she said "porn."
But that means you work in
a really difficult genre!
She said something nice about me...
"To write about sex is
to write about humanity."
I heard a professor say that once.
And I thought, "He's right."
Yes. Yes... That's true!
Well, I believe one day
everyone will come to understand that.
Anyway, let's begin the interview.
Thank you for doing this, Sonokoe-san.
Call me Utae, Taketo-kun.
Okay, Utae-san...
I'd always thought that,
as a pornographic writer, I'd never
have female fans of my own age.
But now, such a wonderful girl...
And a genius idol, who's #1 in school.
She complimented me, and my porno!
That's all for my questions.
Let's take some pictures.
All right. Let's.
Not doing it.
Hold on, Raika. What do you mean,
you're not doing it?
I'm sure it won't be one of those
ugly pictures that you like,
but I don't want to photograph fakes.
Fakes? How is Sonokoe-san a fake?
That's what this is telling me.
Bye.
Raika!
I'm sorry that Raika was so rude.
For a minute, she scared me.
But I guess a genius can tell.
I love this job.
I like dancing and singing, and I think
I'm good at those two things.
And my fans love cheering me on.
I really am grateful for that.
But somewhere deep in my heart,
I've always thought,
"Is this the real me?"
The real you?
My staff and fans are always so kind.
"You're the best," they say.
But is that who I really am?
Aren't I just skating
by, using my talent?
Utae-san...
Sometimes, I feel like
I'm betraying my fans...
and I hate it.
So yesterday's interview
didn't go well, then?
There was nothing I could do about it.
A normal high schooler like me can't do
anything about the problems of a star idol,
the most popular girl in school.
What are you talking about?
You're a genius author yourself,
with fans across the country.
Have some faith in yourself.
Fans, huh?
This is the site of the
World Mathematician's Conference.
By the way, Enshuu Ritsu lectured on the
probability of protrusions in conpeito candy,
and the angles at which they form.
Unfortunately, it's time
for my presentation.
I'm wishing you well from Barcelona.
What present do you want?
Let me see...
Something to do with bullfighting.
I didn't know you were into that.
Yeah, something with a bull and
a swordsman together...
T-Together?
Togeth...
...er.
Why do you...
Even as classmates, that's...
Ritsu! The formula!
Say the magic words to calm yourself!
3... 3.14...
15965...
Ritsu, whatever I said, I'm sorry.
I'm wishing you well from
the Japanese sky, too.
But you know...
Oh? Taketo-san?
How are the interviews proceeding?
No, um, well...
A gentlemen would never run away,
leaving a helpless maiden alone.
That's true! I won't.
Then I'll count on you.
Yes.
They're right.
In a way, isn't Sonokoe-san my
biggest fan in the world?
And I...
Utae-san has the day off. She isn't here
and doesn't plan to come in.
I see. Thank you.
Sonokoe-san?
I don't know.
I see. Thank you.
Have you seen Sonokoe-san?
Why? What do you want from the
school's most popular idol?
To clarify, she isn't someone an enemy
of women everywhere can just hang with—
That's not it!
Because of me, Utae-san's suffering.
I need to talk to her.
I can't abandon her!
Please tell me, Ran!
I-I don't know!
What's with you?! Acting so serious...
Wh-What is this?
Jeez, he's such a pain.
Sonokoe
Is Here
I don't know what's
happening, but good...
Sonokoe
Is Here
Taketo-kun?
Sometimes, when I want to think,
I come to places like these.
This is off the record, okay?
U-Um...
Well... This is...
I don't know anything about
how the world works.
And I always think that, compared to
the rest of the class, I'm just a kid.
No, I...
From the perspective of someone
like you, who has an adult job,
I must seem like a boring kid.
No fantasies. This isn't the time!
Even if the ripen fruit is
blossoming before me,
I must stay strong in the boobs...
I mean, in the face of adversity!
Um, um...
Are you all right? Your face is all red.
Are you sick, maybe?
What is all this?
A novel?
Will you listen to me?
This is a story about a poet and
a songstress with a problem.
The songstress's problem...
It couldn't be solved by a thousand
compliments or ten thousand ovations.
Only the poet understood...
She wanted to push herself further
and further, pass her own limits.
He understood because he, too, was a creator,
and had often encountered those limits.
So the poet began to sing...
for the songstress.
It was the song of the chrysalis.
The chrysalis?
This chrysalis was more beautiful than
any gem in the entire world.
Any who saw it, praised it.
But hidden within, there was an
even more beautiful truth.
Truth?
Wings slumber inside you.
A burst of lightning coursed through
the songstress's body.
Will you stay in that hard,
cramped shell forever?
Is that what you truly desire?
It is not.
The poet's song was like a spider's thread,
catching the songstress's hard, tiny heart.
And wrapping itself around it.
Yes.
The poet continued to sing.
He sang so that she could
be true to herself.
The song became a sharp jaw,
placing its fangs against the
shell surrounding her.
You needn't hide yourself in anything.
Yes.
With quivering hands, the songstress sloughed
off her shell, as if in a strange enchantment.
She no longer saw the
poet himself before her.
A comforting gaze, a
hot breath like fire...
The smell of excitement. His very
existence had become a song.
Her clear skin, that had
captivated millions,
was exposed to the wavering light.
How beautiful...
You're so beautiful.
More. Show me more!
It's all right.
The poet's words were a sweet poison,
spreading through her heart.
And the blue sky was there.
Yes.
The songstress will be reborn.
She will throw off her false cocoon,
to become a free papillon,
and fly off, into the distant blue sky.
As she really exists, in her true form.
Fly! Take flight, to a new world!
Fly!
It was neither fear nor pain,
let alone regret.
It was a height of joy that
she had never known,
an overwhelming feeling of liberation.
The songstress died...
And the true songstress was born.
Thank you, Taketo-kun!
What did I do?
I love you!
I'm in love with you, summer days...
On the night of our love,
lips and summer eyes...
I love you!
She's totally different now.
I'm in love with you, summer days...
Hey!
What? This is the good part.
What happened after that?
What do you mean? I
just reinterviewed her.
And...
And?
What did happen?
I think it was something really good.
What was it again? I forgot!
Are you just a brain and dick?
You're the terrifying dick-man.
You may be right.
Tsukuru-Style stage prop, version 2!
Everyone, thank you!
This time, I learned something too.
That onstage is the real Utae-san.
"The man's thick arms stripped
away her everything,
leaving her free and innocent
as the day of her birth."
"Naked, garbed but by pure eros..."
Naked, huh?
That wasn't only about Utae-san.
It was also about me...
About how I'd been running away,
hiding within a shell of excuses.
I, too, need to be the real me...
The me I want to be.
The real me...
I...
Narukara-san...
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
I'm still an idol, even if I strip!
Preview:
"I Won't Go Away,
I Won't Let You Go"
Preview:
"I Won't Go Away,
I Won't Let You Go"
This is Sonokoe Utae.
When summer heats up,
here's what you need.
A cool feeling in your mouth
and a warm one in your heart.
Your body feels like it's melting.
I can't stop eating them...
Everyone loves the
Inspiration candy bar!