A dream?
The slick, unripe fruit...
Yes, the slick...
N-Narukara-san!
How did this happen?
The story dates back to yesterday morning.
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"I Won't Go Away, I Won't Let You Go"
Today, I'll tell Narukara-san
the truth and apologize to her.
What's going on here?
Wh-What is this?!
Come to the teacher's office for a moment.
Taketo-kun,
I understand that you're a
boy going through puberty.
I know that you're having
a lot of different feelings,
but for you to do that!
I already explained. There was this rocket...
Your nose was bleeding.
You still want to keep this up?
Impressive, Mr. King Freak.
When I fell, I hit my nose.
Anyway, whose fault do you think
it is that all this happened?
I just released the photos publicly.
I never said anyone did anything.
Don't you think your everyday behavior
has something to do with this?
Is this true?
I don't know.
Answer me honestly, Narukara-san.
What did Taketo-kun do to you?
He ate it.
Y-Y-Y-You ate her?
That's a lie, right, Taketo?
Tell me it's a lie!
How dare you...
Please let go!
I'm going to kill him and then myself!
I'll kill myself!
Calm down, Onee-sama. Not here! Not here!
I don't believe it... Taketo wouldn't do that!
Aki-sensei, give me some time.
I'll prove his innocence.
Please!
Fine.
Giving students a lot of latitude is part
of Inspiration Academy's motto.
Once the details are clearer,
I'll determine his punishment.
T-Teacher...
But if you're guilty, after all...
Death
Penalty
Prepare yourself.
This is really bad...
I don't think I'm even going to
survive until the punishment.
Don't worry.
I won't let anyone touch you until
we discover the truth behind those photos.
Ritsu...
And I really dislike just
assuming a person's guilt.
You want to be sure to do it right?
T-To do it?
What are you talking about?
I mean, this really isn't a big deal.
Don't take it the wrong way.
I just—
Ritsu! The formula!
3.141592...
A rocket?
So you were in its path? I didn't even notice.
Surely, you have some kind of
video or something, right?
Would you show me?
No, it's a pain.
I'm busy running a check
on my latest invention.
Here it is!
Mr. Sticky!
Mr. Sticky?
Mr. Sticky is amazing.
A pigeon-wrench!
Pigeon
Wrench
Its sub-unit emits special magnetic waves,
which stick something to anything else.
Stick together...
Combine!
A Drill
A Drill Is
A Man's Romance!
Combine! Combine! Combine! Combine!
No!
Docking.
So surprised, you can't even speak?
Tell me about it another time.
You still don't understand
how great Mr. Sticky really is.
Okay, power up!
Huh?
Stay away!
Smack!
Ow...
This really has gotten interesting.
That hurts. It hurts... It really hurts!
Come on...
This isn't working at all!
It's totally broken...
Let go of Fukune-chan!
You let go!
What is this?
Oh, right. Why not remove your clothes?
I-I see.
Okay, I'll do it.
No!
You strip, Taketo...
You like it anyway, for your job.
Take your clothes off!
Wh-What are you saying? Taketo can't
remove his clothes in public...
Stop. I'll do it.
Taketo?
As anticipated...
The only way to solve this
is by fixing the machine.
How long will repairs take?
Who knows? A day? A year?
No way!
Seriously?
Just relax.
I won't interfere, no matter what happens.
N-No matter what?
I'm not letting anything happen!
I can't relax...
C-Come to think of it, it's the first time
a girl's been in my room!
I can't fantasize about anything!
Due to unforeseen events,
we now present
The Best of Akutagawa Taketo's Fantasies.
Come in...
T-Teacher...
Teacher!
Wh-What is this?
I can't be thinking about that now!
This is my chance to apologize to Narukara-san.
N-N-Narukara-san...
Molester Train: Straight-on, Toward A Nal.
What is that?
S-Stuff for a book about trains!
Oh, no.
My room is really dangerous!
It's a powder keg of porn.
"I'll send you the documents you requested."
Fax spam!
C-Could I clean my room?
Sure.
Let me go!
Onee-sama, calm down...
I can't leave Fukune-chan stuck
in that den of iniquity!
You have a lot of research material.
Y-Yeah? I don't really know.
Authors are amazing.
No... Th-That's not true.
But now, I can talk to her calmly.
Um...
Y-You first.
Could I practice?
Practice?
Yeah.
What's that?
That emblem-like thing?
Is it some kind of special clarinet?
I was just curious...
It's fine if you don't want to say.
It was a gift...
From someone important to me.
S-Someone important?
My dad.
Your dad?
I see... Your dad, huh?
But practice? You really still need
to practice, even like this?
You can't stop practicing the clarinet,
not even for a single day.
I see...
But isn't it tough, getting motivated every day?
Like if you're tired...
On days like that, I think you should do something
to cheer up and refresh yourself.
I see...
So that's how it is for everyone.
Hello?
Hello.
U-Utae-san?
Sounds like this is pretty bad.
Yeah, um, well...
Lots of people I know are
making a big deal over it.
I wonder why.
You'd never do that.
Utae-san, thank you!
Anyway, Taketo-kun...
Yes?
Is someone there with you?
N-Not really!
Anyway, my editor's coming over!
Sorry! I'll talk to you later!
But thanks for calling! Bye!
Why am I lying?
Anyway, this is amazing...
It's as if the music is seeping into my heart.
Was I bothering you?
No.
Huh?
I can't do it...
I-It's okay! Just think of me as
a rock or chair or something.
Okay.
I'm a rock. I'm not here... I'm not here!
Taketo's having such a miserable time.
Isn't there... Isn't there anything that I can do?
I-It's over.
I hope she got to practice...
Narukara-san, I wanted to talk to you.
She fell asleep, huh?
It really is late.
Narukara-san...
My draft! I need a new copy of my draft!
I see nothing here but work.
And what I don't see doesn't exist!
It doesn't count as having seen it!
"His breath was like a pair of bellows.
It was a cry of lust,
swollen with desire and passion.
Another beast was furiously rising.
It was he, himself, shining with carnal desire."
Desire... Lust... Beast...
Carnal... Shining...
I didn't see you! I didn't see you, so forgive me!
Shining... Shining... Shining...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Once again, we're changing plans,
to present
The Best of Akutagawa Taketo's Fantasies.
N-No...
A night touchdown!
Hut! Hut!
Good morning!
I completed the repairs.
Get up, Narukara-san!
Did you really fix it?
Hey, you don't believe me?
It's fine...
Mr. Sticky Custom!
I didn't just fix it!
In the end, I never did talk to her.
I feel bad, but there's nothing I can do.
And its effective radius is...
Just do it, already!
You sure?
All right, switch on!
Huh?
Look at that!
This one isn't working, either.
Taketo! Fukune-chan!
This is even crazier.
Narukara-san!
Stop! My clarinet!
Give it back...
Let go, Taketo! It'll take you with it, too!
Don't do it, even if you die!
If you don't die, I'll kill you!
Ow!
Let go!
Don't let go!
O-Ouch...
I can't hold on...
It doesn't hurt! It doesn't hurt!
I-It feels really good.
I-It feels good, but it hurts!
It feels good, but it hurts!
Yay! Yay!
Yay! Yay...
Here you go.
You saved it for me?
It's really important to you, isn't it?
U-Um...
There's something I wanted
to talk to you about.
Taketo!
Are you all right, Fukune-chan?
Yeah.
He protected it.
But what about those photos?
Oh, those?
Look... He was just trying to save her.
I refuse to accept it!
Someday, I will catch you.
So I guess everything's over.
No... If you'd just shown that
to everyone from the start,
none of this would have happened.
When I was investigating you, I got interested.
You destroyed my machine with a nosebleed!
That's so marvelous! So perverted!
I'm not really happy about those compliments.
Hey, let me dissect you?
I-I'll see you later!
No way... Dissect me?
N-Narukara-san!
U-Um...
Yes?
What did you want to talk to me about?
A-A lot of things.
But about that reed...
Um, I didn't mean to...
I was really hungry!
So...
No, it's all right now. I understand.
Because...
Back there, you were so serious.
You wouldn't have eaten it.
I was wrong. I'm sorry.
I-It's fine.
H-Huh?
I see. Narukara-san is always practicing here.
It feels so good...
Like it's warming my heart.
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
My rocket's really cold...
Hey! Kagaku Tsukuru here.
Next time:
"Photo Stories"
Ta-dah!
It's a Tsukuru-Style buzz-buzz machine!
Watch when I do this.
Bam! Bam! Bam!
It's like a machine gun!
Ratta-tat-tat!
Bang! Bang! Bang!
That's what it does.