It's bright.
It's so hot.
Why is this the scene that I'm waking up to?!
Is this a reward the Porno-God has given me for all my hard work?
It's on this side, too!
Thank you, God!
Yay, I'm-
No fucking way!
What's going on?!
Where am I?
No!
Utae-san.
Unbelievable...
Taketo-kun would do something like this...
I... I...
Huh?
No, no, no!
I didn't do anything obscene!
She was like this when I woke up!
Raika-san... lap pillow...
Narukara-san!
It's not what you think it is,
I don't know what's going on either...
Is it morning already?
Hey, Taketo-kun, you weren't really...
You disgusting pornovelist!
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"An R15 Boy's Castaway Tale"
What about over there?
Nope.
Only airplane debris is left.
I can't see any of the other students or our luggage.
Over there too.
Could it be... everyone was...
Don't cry, Utae-san!
Although we don't know for sure,
my instincts as a genius porn novelist tell me that everyone is all right!
There's no need to worry!
My clarinet...
I'm sure we'll be able to find it, Narukara-san!
Anyway, we should take care of our situation here first.
That's true.
However, before that...
Let's take another photo of the perverted pornovelist.
I already said that it was a misunderstanding...
In that unbelievable new student orientation tournament,
we won and were given a trip to Vienna.
It's really amazing!
Narukara-san's clarinet!
It's all thanks to Taketo-kun.
Naw...
You were the one who drew the graffiti?!
Shut up. This isn't the time or the place for that.
But it was great.
Coincidentally, my recital was there at the same time.
I was really shocked when I suddenly received the tickets.
Sorry for being so sudden.
But it was fun to go to so many places together.
Right.
So how should I say this...
What a frightening coincidence...
Yeah. The world is full of beautiful coincidences.
How scary!
But on the return flight...
Everyone, calm down!
So, back to the present.
Where are we?
This seems to be an unpopulated tropical island.
Anyway, let's try to find the others.
Since there's airplane debris, the others must also be safely on the ground.
Right, of course!
But, what was that gigantic UFO-shaped thing?
If it's someone from our school, it wouldn't be surprising to have such an ability.
Even so, we don't understand the intentions behind doing that.
Maybe it could be an actual UFO,
with the goal of merely exterminating on all witnesses.
Something like Cattle Mutilation.
Don't say something so scary, Raika.
Cattle... what?
It's an urban legend that says when animals are abducted,
strange experiments are done,
like removing all blood...
The content and illustrations are completely mismatched!
I see...
Narukara-san, what are you doing...
Did they do any reconstructive surgery?
I don't want something weird to be done to me!
Uh, Narukara-san.
Hey, Taketo-kun.
Is there something wrong with me?
Eh?!
Is there?
Um...
Oh right, you can't see it if I'm wearing underwear.
Wait a minute, Narukara-san, you're fine!
Also, why are you stripping from the bottom?!
But if you don't look properly, I'll be scared.
Taketo-kun, please check me properly...
Uh, the story just now was just a...
Taketo-kun!
Why is Utae-san also-
What are you doing?!
I also want Taketo-kun to...
Um... please check me...
No, no!
Forget about the aliens! Even so, why me?
Hey, hurry up.
I just want Taketo-kun!
Oh, right. It'll be easier if I take off my underwear.
Wait, did you hear me?!
Wait!
Taketo-kun.
Hey, hurry up.
Under the blazing sun,
waves pushing after waves in the azure ocean...
My heart was full of waves as well.
Why are you... you two...?
Come on, Taketo-kun, you strip too.
It's because we're the only ones here.
Right?
Taketo-kun, hurry up!
It's coming!
Then the two seduced me even more brazenly!
I really am a genius!
Geez...
Hey, didn't I say that it would be better to search along the coastlines?
If we were just trying to find the others, that would be enough.
However, we have to make sure that there's fresh water,
because we don't know how long we're gonna be stuck here.
Even so, it's too hot out here.
My throat is starting to get dry...
Yeah...
I think in a place like this, there would be...
Sorry.
Here, Narukara-san.
Don't drink it, just swirl it in your mouth.
It may not be suitable for drinking.
Amazing, Taketo-kun!
How did you know that?
I'm not a novelist for nothing, you know.
I know some relevant general knowledge, too.
A failed writer?
There's an incorrect adjective there!
What was that sound?!
I'm not sure.
But in this jungle, it wouldn't be surprising for something to be here.
What do you mean, "something"?
Will I get eaten?
That's not...
That's way beyond the level of having "something here"...
What is it this time?!
That sound, could it be-
How?
Dammit, come save me!
Ran-san!
No, No...
Real tentacle play!
Taketo-kun, if we don't save her quickly...
Right!
No!
Everyone!
No! Stop! It's disgusting!
Dammit, you pervert!
Stupid Taketo!
Hey, don't say my name like that!
Shut up, you're a synonym for pervert!
Looks like we've enraged it.
Looks like all monsters hate being called Taketo.
My existence is so...
Don't!
Amazing, I don't need any mental images now!
Everything that's before me is real enough!
Is there something to write with here?
Taketo-kun...
What an admirable pervert professionalism...
Save us, Taketo-kun!
Almost forgot.
Hey, let them go!
You monst-
Huh?
O-Ouch...
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Stop!
Ritsu, you're all right?
I will never forgive anything that hurts Taketo!
Be careful, Ritsu!
This guy is a pervert!
Him
-
Don't wory.
I can easily analyze the tentacle movements with mathematics!
'Sup, Taketo.
What the hell was that?!
I've had enough!
Don't eat me!
I don't taste good!
Let her go!
Eat me if you want!
No, that's not what I mean by eat!
I see, it's bicurious when it comes to food.
Well said, but this is bad!
I'm a little turned on...
Stop, who would want to see this?!
Come on, come on, Taketo!
Fight, fight, come on!
That's...
Katsuyo-chan?
Why is she here too?!
Now let's try this!
Is everyone all right?
Tsukuru's here too? But how?
You should've used something safer.
It's fine if everyone is all right.
How can you say that when we look like this?
Paradise...
Don't look, demon of lust!
Hurry up and find us some clothes!
Even if you say so...
Where would we find any in this jungle?
Huh?
Why is there a chest there?
Defeating a monster will cause it to drop loot!
Although it's usually just useless potions...
But occasionally, there's armor.
If we find some, you guys can wear it.
Th-This is...
Amazing, what a nice place!
I've never seen such a huge lake!
However, why did the chest contain these things?
We didn't have anything to wear, so isn't it fine?
Tsukuru-chan and the others found fresh water, too.
Let's conquer this lake first!
What ugly ambition.
The fish are chasing me!
Fukune-chan, feel this!
It's ice-cold!
Wouldn't it be fine to stay here forever?
That's it.
These will be our temporary job allocations.
Logs - Taketo
Shelter - Raika
Food - Ritsu
Logs - Utae-san
Food - Katsuyo-san
Shelter - Narukara-san
Shelter -
Tsukuru will be in charge of building sleeping quarters.
Got it!
Leave it to me!
Although I'm worried about the other students, it's good to have a base first.
Right. It isn't a good idea to just search randomly.
My clarinet...
You're still talking about that, kid?
Oh, right. Why are you guys here?
And why are you in a gym uniform?
I was testing this at school.
Then something like a UFO suddenly showed up.
I was here when I woke up.
Then Katsuyo-san is here because of a UFO, too?
I was done cheering for the Judo club and was changing, when...
When?
Um... I forgot!
Oh, really.
Hey, Taketo-kun,
it's hard to say if it's just us,
but everyone related has seen a UFO, could it be...?
Yeah. I thought of the chief as well.
This incident is...
I can't say for sure.
I don't know the motive behind this either, however...
There's a great relationship between UFOs and legs!
Huh, legs?
UFO! I meant UFOs!
Yes. That's it!
Taketo-kun!
Sorry! Sorry! I got a little excited...
Didn't I already say that if you wanted to see them, you can just say it?
What a beautiful scene!
It'd be better if we weren't stranded.
Also, Utae-san is really unlucky.
Eh?
If you didn't see us is Vienna by coincidence,
this wouldn't have happened.
It's not coincidence.
Didn't you have a recital?
That was a lie.
I actually went there chasing after Taketo-kun.
Wait, Utae-san?
Nope, that was a lie!
A lie? Wait. Which one?
All of it!
Sorry, Taketo-kun.
Don't scare me...
I'm... such a liar.
What is this?
Dunno.
It seems to be a fighter plane from a long time ago.
World War II, the American navy's main bomber, Avenger.
Chief?!
What's up?
It's great that you're all okay.
What's going on?!
What might you be referring to?
Don't avoid the topic.
You brought us to this island...
No matter how brazen I am,
I wouldn't take down a plane.
So why is the chief here?
I don't know any more than you.
I came here without knowing anything.
According to legend, in December of 1945,
five Avengers disappeared in an aerial training exercise.
The location of that is...
The Bermuda Triangle?
The magnetic field, a missing 4th dimenson, etc.
There are various theories.
There are also theories about aliens.
Regardless of how,
planes and ships have disappeared and never found.
Don't say that, you'll scare everyone.
There's no point in thinking anything now.
On another topic,
if we don't hurry up, the sun will set.
Is that the gigantic fella?
We've got to set up camp fast.
Right, let's do that!
Hey, Taketo, give directions!
You scared me!
Is Taketo-kun not going to eat?
I'll eat later, you can go eat first.
Is that a weapon?
It doesn't look like much,
but it's better than nothing, right?
Here!
Say "ah".
What is it, Narukara-san?
If you don't eat, you won't have any spirit.
So say "ah".
Thanks.
See you later.
How's the banana that tastes like Narukara?
Are you a ninja?!
Narukara has really changed.
Between Sonokoe and Narukara, which one will you choose?
Wh-What are you talking about?
No one knows what will happen next.
The time to make a choice will come quickly.
Although this is a really nice scene for a porn novelist...
I'm still too weak...
Taketo, over here!
What is that?
I don't know.
We just happened to find this when looking for everyone.
It seems to be some kind of ruins.
This isn't an uninhabited island?
But we can be sure something is here.
What does that door lead to?
Something might be buried underground.
So, can we open it?
I don't know.
It's that sound again.
It's really close!
Is this the guy that was making those sounds?
Everyone, run!
That's too fast!
Come on, Taketo!
No!
Narukara-san!
No, Fukune-chan!
Wait, hey!
Come back! Give me Narukara-san!
Narukara-san!
Narukara-san!!
Dammit.
Taketo...
It's fine no matter what happens to me.
Narukara-san, I'll definitely save you!
I found it!
It's eating something humongous!
Fukune-chan!
She looks fine for now.
Look over there!
So that's what happened.
Looks like everyone is here.
That's great.
However, as long as that thing is still there,
we can't go in.
Because of that shot yesteday, I'm all out of ammo.
We can distract that thing from some distance first.
Then we can...
What are the chances of bait escaping from that?
No matter what we do,
it will be difficult to rescue both Fukune-san and the other students at the same time.
We can't have our cake and eat it too.
If we make the wrong choice...
There will be no choice.
We'll rescue all of them.
You're such an idiot.
So what will we do?
It's not a normal foe.
I have my own way of fighting.
Hey, are you an idiot?!
How can speaking to that thing work?!
I understand, Taketo-san.
That being said, please use this.
Thank you very much.
Taketo-kun!
Chapter One:
A Popular Idol's Wet & Wild Photoshoot!
How nice!
Lower your head a litte more.
Right, just like that.
Okay.
All right, now try stripping.
Huh? I didn't hear about the nude part...
Nude is the only true gravure art.
Come on, let me see the real you!
Yes!
Merely delivering a smile and a healthy body,
will never satisfy the fans.
In the photoshoot,
Show me everything...
Knock me out...
The lust can't be contained.
Yes, that's the right expression!
Look!
Look at all of me!
No way. It's working!
Seriously?!
Eros is the instinct of all animals!
It can cross every single barrier,
giving the power of a direct attack!
Next is Chapter Two:
Way To Make The Perfect Android ! !
The Way To Make The Perfect Android ! !
Let's Do It!!
Do Androids Dream of Ero Sheep?
The Way To Make The Perfect Android ! !
Let's Do It!!
A manmade android lacks emotional senses.
The Way To Make The Perfect Android ! !
Let's Do It!!
Especially taste and touch.
The Way To Make The Perfect Android ! !
Let's Do It!!
That's why...
The Way To Make The Perfect Android ! !
Hey, what are you trying to do to me?!
I think "boku" girls are cute.
The most basic of human emotions is eros.
If you don't understand ero,
there can be no way to breathe new life into things.
Get even more turned on.
You're the genius inventor, right?
No!
It's coming! Coming!
My inspiration is coming!
Yes, good job, Taketo!
Amazing!
Although I don't understand what's going on...
Take him out, Taketo!
Chapter Three:
Definite Destiny, Office Love!
Definitely impossible.
Forgive me.
It's already your third year. If you're still like this...
Looks like it's time to discipline you again.
Y-Yes...
Seriously, I hope you're not making these mistakes on purpose.
No, it's nothing like that.
Really?
Give me an honest answer.
It's true!
I... I'm...
Really?
Then...
You're already like this...
Give it up! Come on!
I'm very sorry!
Please humiliate me, the lowly worm!
Please! I beg you!
This is also having an effect. That means...
That thing seems to be a huge masochist.
Wait, Narukara-san.
I will save you now!
Chapter Four:
Clarinet Lesson of Lust!
Oh no, I keep screwing up at the same part.
Don't give up!
You have to keep calm and focused at all times!
I'll help you!
Let's work hard together!
No, d-don't!
I can't play this way!
Come on, Fukune-chan, work hard!
That's not all right.
If you can't focus...
But...
This will get you to work harder!
If you can get past this, you'll definitely be able to improve!
Work hard, work hard!
Just a little more, Taketo!
Not bad, Taketo-sensei.
Taketo-kun!
Eros is truth!
Final Chapter:
How about this?!
Narukara-san!
Fukune-chan!
Are you all right, Narukara-san?
Sorry for coming so late...
What is this?!
What's going on?
No. I know what this is.
Chief!
Chief? Where is she?!
Who would have thought that the pinnacle of biological engineering would lose?
I was really shocked.
The genius of ero indeed.
Genius Porno Author
"Akutagawa Taketo's R-15 Young Boy Travelogue"
Production Assistant Notes
That's why it was exciting.
If he finds out that everything was to get him inspiration for writing a book,
he'll be pretty shocked.
We pretty much transformed the entire island.
We set up a replacement, too.
Um, can you hear me?
Ero Da Best!
A new erotic novel born under extreme conditions.
For this, I am willing to even become the devil.
We can see that guy's ugly mug again soon.
Then, let's go into the next phase!
There're plenty of mechanisms on that island!
Work hard!
Punch it!
What's going on now?
When can we finally get back?!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta