They know they're not meant
for others to view,
but girls are always ready to
show them off anyway.
With brilliant colors, cute patterns,
and a powerful sexuality,
they invite the attention of foolish insects...
The irresistible urge that compels
one to look, heedless of danger.
Thus, men call them "The Forbidden Garden."
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Photo Stories"
I did a great job yesterday.
Trying to fantasize based purely
on a photograph is really fun...
Good morning.
N-Narukara-san!
G-Good morning!
I-It's nice out today.
Yes, it really is nice...
This is it!
The school life I've dreamed of
has finally begun!
What's wrong?
Your eyes are red.
Were you working all night?
Y-Yeah,
I guess so...
I'd still like to read your
romance novels, sometime.
Th-That's right...
Narukara-san doesn't know
I'm a porno author yet.
I don't read very much,
but if it's something a friend from class wrote...
D-Don't force yourself.
You're busy with clarinet practice, right?
But...
Keep at your music.
I'll be much happier that way.
Really? Then I will.
Anyway, I'm off to the music wing. Bye!
You're pathetic.
You write those horribly dirty novels,
and let everyone except Narukara-san know?
Wh-Who cares, really?
The moment an innocent girl awakens
to the dirty adult world...
It's the perfect photographic subject.
That doesn't have anything
to do with Narukara-san.
You don't understand.
Humans are ugly creatures.
Especially women.
You're the one who doesn't understand, Raika.
This is...
one of those "love letters" I've heard of!
What do you think?
It's possible that it really is a love letter.
This? Seriously?
There are people who want to skip the
love process and jump right to the end.
In other words,
they want to skip the
initial meeting and dates,
and just want to XX me?
It's pretty awful.
They're trying to ensnare Taketo,
using a cunning plan...
A love letter!
Could I actually be...
Lucky!
NEWSPAPER
CIRCLE
You got the draft in well before
the deadline, and it looks good.
You've been doing a good job lately.
Yeah, I guess.
Raika-san, how's that other job going?
Not done yet.
Other job?
I asked her to make a poster
for Inspiration Academy.
Come to
Inspiration
Academy
Come to
Inspiration
Academy
To attract geniuses next year,
from across Japan...
I wanted something avant-garde and stunning,
a photo that people would never forget.
I know that, but...
I can't get the kind of picture I want...
A slump? That's rare.
What?
It's nothing.
I don't know who sent this.
And I don't know what this person looks like.  My only clue is the bear panties!
And then we all got together and worked on it!
But even so...
I can't just ask them to
show me their panties.
A divine wind!
Blue... Pink.
Too bad!
What's too bad?
I'll try harder! I'm sorry!
The legendary striped panties!
Close! It's not a bear. It's a spotted snake.
Amazing! Strawberry Panic!
What's been happening today?
It's exactly like those normal high school
lives I read about in manga!
But I haven't found the bear yet.
That's it...
My desire to find the girl in the photograph
has awakened a psychic power within me!
I am the man who summons the divine wind—
Look at all these complaints!
Everyone's claiming you flipped up their skirts.
That was a misunderstanding.
I didn't do anything.
If you admit it, I might let you off
with a hundred lashes.
It was a divine wind!
Enough!
I refuse to believe that a whirlwind
is following you around.
An adult black!
You pervert problematic child!
That was mean.
All else aside, that one was a total accident.
You are cursed.
Yoruno Misa
Genius
Fortune Teller
The line between good luck
and bad is very thin.
Yoruno Misa
Genius
Fortune Teller
Wh-What?
Yoruno Misa?
I've heard her bad predictions
always come true.
But so far, it feels like I've been
lucky with everything.
You really think so?
If you get close to him,
you'll end up humiliated.
Even within a meter is dangerous.
That's terrible! I was just cleared
of the last scandal...
Good
Luck
Bad
Good
Luck
Bad
Good
Luck
Bad
Wh-What should I do?
That photo...
Y-You think it's cursed or something?
I don't believe in anything
as unscientific as curses.
But if I were to speculate,
then I'd suspect a plot,
using the appearance of a curse.
A plot? Whose?
Normally, I'd say whoever
most profits from these events...
You mean I'm making it all up?
I believe you, of course!
Taketo, you're going after me, too?
Th-That was an accident! I didn't do it.
"Do it"?
I couldn't... Not here...
Ritsu, the formula...
Say the magic words!
3.141...
I have to do something.
What?
You cannot escape the curse.
The real hell is just beginning.
Are you... the one behind this?
I just see the future.
And I see you suffering...
W-Wait!
No... I guess it wasn't you.
Come to think of it, everything
so far has involved panties.
If I really am cursed, I have
to look out for panties.
L-Lucky!
Th-This is...
The smell of detergent.
They must be freshly washed.
Are these yours?
Yes, I dropped them.
But there isn't any proof they're yours.
If you want proof, I have it.
They simply need to fit me perfectly.
Now, try putting them on me.
You're some Cinderella, you know that?
I can see it now!
I'll call it "The Glass Panties." But wait,
then there's no point in wearing them.
Oh, no.
I was taken in by the panties.
No, no. If I carry these,
something else terrible will happen.
Someone's laundry must've blown away.
I'll give them to one of the guards.
Who are you?!
No... Stop it!
A dream?
Go, go, Inspiration! Let's go, Inspiration!
M-More panties!
Oh, so fast!
Someone save me!
Only
Girls
How dare you?
I-It wasn't me!
Who else is here?
How dare you expose my secret?
It's a misunderstanding!
And anyway, everyone already knows.
You piece of trash!
Th-That would've killed me!
Go back to hell!
That hurt...
I never thought you'd see
through my ninja skills.
Kagaku Tsukuru?
That was really mean...
You broke my Divine Wind Machine.
What are you doing?
What's a Divine Wind Machine?
My new invention!
It causes local gusts of wind!
It was you? It was you all along?
Let me explain.
First, it uses microwaves to deconstruct
the air, at the atomic level...
Why are you doing this?
Meiki-san asked me to!
Raika? She was behind everything?
Raika!
What the hell were you thinking?
Raika?
What are these?
I'm disappointed in you!
You've been photographing me?
I gave you my underwear, and that's
the best photo you can give me?
Those were your panties?
Then, that picture...
Was the bear not sexy enough?
Even if it was only temporary,
I was excited by Raika's panties...
What do you mean by that?
What do you have against me?
It's all your fault!
Is this the true identity of the
perverted fetish author
that people call "The Lust That Walks"?
The man whom all woman avoid,
the man who inhabits a world
of his own fantasies.
What happened to the abnormal
hikikomori, Akutagawa Takuto?
That's how you've been thinking of me?
Until you take back that disgusting,
twisted light of yours,
you're not worth photographing.
My life as a cameraman is over.
I'm causing your slump?
Of course!
Why the hell do you want an
ugly photo for that poster?
You'll scare everyone away
from Inspiration Academy!
That's the problem!
I'm taking that photo, no matter what.
I was wrong to think that
taking my photos secretly
was the way to expose
humanity's true nature.
I'll take an ugly picture,
with you as my model.
Y-You're kidding, right?
If you refuse, I'll publicize this photo.
That would be bad.
I doubt I could talk my way out of that one.
Please let me help you.
This will be our photo studio.
Why the girl's bathroom?
This is holy ground, where no man may tread.
And now a perverted, impotent
jackass is sneaking in to taint it.
Now, violate the woman's restroom,
where maidens are most defenseless,
with your ugly, disgusting fantasies!
How am I supposed to violate
a woman's bathroom?
Am I supposed to have some kind
of building fetish?
Stop talking and get to work!
You know...
That isn't ugly at all!
If you're only sitting on a toilet,
it looks like you're doing a #2.
There's no point in being
in the women's bathroom!
Of course not.
Do something! You're a
genius pornographic author.
Like what? If a girl isn't using it,
it isn't a girl's bathroom!
So you want me sitting there?
A man who breaks in and watches
a girl while she urinates.
I see. That's very ugly.
All right.
W-W-Wait!
I'm a professional. I'm prepared
to give myself for a photo.
Wait, wait. You can't do that!
Art demands sacrifice!
Taketo-kun?
U-Utae-san...
What are you doing, you pervert?
I'm not!
Raika made me...
Don't leave me!
You pervert!
You won't be able to talk
your way out of this one.
This was just...
Wait, everyone!
Don't jump to conclusions.
He could be here for his novel.
No, but...
I don't think that's a
good excuse, though.
Wh-What?
Manager...
I'm soaked.
Down there, too?
Take it off.
The fans want to play with your naughty water.
Okay... If it's for the fans...
N-No!
That's it! Go!
The perverted fetish author who'd violate
a wet idol in the girl's bathroom...
That's my Akutagawa Taketo.
Raika!
I was lucky they forgave me, but...
What were you doing?
I was so close to taking a
wonderfully ugly picture.
You chicken!
Why do you obsess so much
over ugly photographs?
I take ugly photographs.
I have to.
Why?
We'll start again tomorrow.
Bye.
Don't involve anyone else in this!
Nothing is taboo when it comes to art.
I have to do something about this...
Damn you, Raika!
Saying all that stuff...
I'll do this to you, and this, and this!
Girl's Locker Room
The sweet smell of sweat and deodorant...
Why are we in the girl's locker room?
This is holy ground, where no man may tread.
And now a perverted, exhibitionist
author is sneaking in to taint it.
Now, violate the girl's locker room,
where girls expose everything,
with your ugly, disgusting fantasies.
This is the same stuff you said
in the girl's bathroom.
You're not improving.
Shut up!
Get to work!
Hell, no!
Violate it, already! Damn it!
What are you doing?
Get started! I'll preserve your
ugliest moment for eternity.
I can't!
Do it! Do it now!
She's nuts!
I see... You don't have enough
fantasy material, right?
H-Hey!
Looks like pictures and freshly washed
panties aren't enough for you.
What do you think?
Better than the photo, right?
Actually pretty cute...
I didn't think Raika'd look good
in something like that.
I'll give you these, freshly worn.
That must be good enough, right?
Indeed!
Wait, that's really bad!
As a cameraman, my job is to do
whatever it takes for the photo.
D-Don't take that off!
Do you plan to take me?
No, um...
I didn't expect you to be the one taking it.
I-I'm sorry!
You chicken!
If you can't do it, I will!
S-Stop...
What?
I'm the only one this will hurt.
I... I...
They're watching me.
My ugliness...
I'm watching.
Raika?
Don't look at me!
No! Don't look at me!
The female cameraman realized
a million eyes were on her.
And that everything about her was being revealed.
She could hide nothing.
Because that was what she wanted.
She wished to be seen.
No!
She was waiting...
to be displayed...
Displayed in all her shamefulness.
What she wanted to photograph,
more than anything,
was right before her.
Show them. Show them...
How ugly you are!
Show yourself!
Ugly...
I am ugly.
You're ugly!
Raika!
I finished the poster, Taketo.
Looks like you're out of your slump.
Yeah. I think I'm over it.
I feel better.
It's thanks to you.
No, well...
I'm glad.
Look at this!
It's perfect.
Wh-What is this?
It's my way of saying thanks.
How?
Aren't you embarrassed?
The greatest cameraman makes
for the greatest subject.
Right?
Then just photograph yourself.
Since we're both ugly,
don't you think we make a good pair?
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
Don't spill it!
I'm the one they'll get mad at.
Next Time:
"Beyond Friends with Benefits"
This is Meiki Raika.
Not there! How many times must I tell you?
That's not where it itches...
Are you an idiot at this?
Not there! Hey!
Don't touch that!