Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
That isn't me!
Everyone's trying so hard.
I can't be the only one who runs away!
"I Love You!!"
I don't want her to find out...
I don't want her to hate me!
But does that mean I can let her suffer?
Am I just going to ignore her feelings,
and tell myself pretty lies, so I feel better?
I'm going to write!
I'll write, so she can laugh again.
I'll write, so she can play her clarinet again.
This time, I'll do what I can do...
What only I can do!
I'm going to write...
to the very end!
I love your music!
I can't do anything...
I don't know anything.
So why?
No!
This isn't right!
I hate everything about it!
Narukara-san...
I won't lie to you anymore.
The real me...
Akutagawa-kun!
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
Taketo-kun...
I have to find Narukara-san.
I'm totally out of blood...
Please take this.
Give it to Narukara-san, in class 3.
Thank you...
It's time for the final battle of
the orientation tournament!
This is the final round.
Show us your genius potential.
We'll start things off...
...with an opening ceremony!
Yay!
How long will you throw this tantrum?
We're leaving.
It's almost time for our performance.
What is he doing?!
That pervert!
H-He can't...
He'll come! I know he will!
Of course he will!
Ow...
Akutagawa-kun!
Taketo!
Taketo, I knew you'd come!
Stop...
That was a dance performance by
the first-year cheerleaders.
Now, who's up first?
Class 1-1!
Is something wrong, ma'am?
Please hurry.
Wait just a moment.
Wh-What is this?
This is too much...
We did ask for porn lyrics.
Even I'm a little turned off by this.
That's why she'll listen. With Kanade-san's music
and Narukara-san's accompaniment,
it'd make anyone stand erect and listen!
Erect?
That's my power!
Taketo...
If you're that sure of it,
we'll follow you to the end!
Right, everyone?
That's right.
Let's do it.
Yeah!
All that's left is Narukara-san.
I'm sure she'll come... Definitely.
Did you need something?
May I have a moment?
Y-Yes...
This is for you.
I'm waiting
We're leaving.
Fukune!
Miss...
Miss Fukune!
Let's look up at the sky.
Where's Utae-san?
Where did she go?
What do we do?
An ill omen...
I'm sorry to make you help me
with this, Tsukuru-chan.
It's fine...
I'm happy, as long as I get my research funds!
After all, I'm a mad scientist
who will destroy the world!
Thank you.
Bye.
I'm sorry, everyone.
But...
Whatever happens, you should be
honest about your feelings.
This is all I can do.
No matter what.
Th-There's no time left...
Narukara-san.
U-Um, I...
I've been waiting for you, Fukune-chan!
Everything's fine... I'm with you.
Now, let's go.
Let's go, Class 3!
Fukune...
And our last act for the day...
...is class 1-3!
Akutagawa-kun.
Narukara-san...
This is who I really am.
This is Akutagawa Taketo!
kuchukuchu
くちゅくちゅ
In and out.
nuru nuru
ヌルヌル
Slick and wet.
munyu munyu
むにゅむにゅ
Soft and round.
shikoshiko
シコシコ
Stroking hard.
nante suteki
なんて素敵
How wonderful.
kuchukuchu
くちゅくちゅ
In and out.
nuru nuru
ヌルヌル
Slick and wet.
munyu munyu
むにゅむにゅ
Soft and round.
shikoshiko
シコシコ
Stroking hard.
The disjunction between music
and lyrics is funny...
motto chupachupa
もっとチュパチュパ
Keep on sucking
kannou no eden e to kokoro wa odori
官能のエデンへと心は踊り
My heart dances toward endless pleasure,
ichiban no suki na basho wo tadoritsuku
一番の好きな場所を辿り着く
reaching the place I love the most.
kidzuitara deatta hi mousou shiteta
気付いたら出会った日　妄想してた
Next thing I know, I'm thinking
of the day we met,
umareta manma no sugata sarashite
生まれたまんまの姿晒して
naked as the day we were born.
kairaku no merodii ni hajirau megami
快楽のメロディーに恥らう女神
A goddess, blushing at the melody of pleasure,
shinayakana gosenfu ni sosoritatsu
しなやかな五線譜にそそり立つ
a pillar standing erect between lithe curves...
suteeji ni hibiku koe aegu toiki
ステージに響く声　喘ぐ吐息
A voice loud and clear across the stage,
a hot and gasping breath.
afuredasu neiro wa yokubou
溢れ出す音色は欲望
The melody I'm hearing is desire.
nugisutetara saa ikou yo mitsu no ogawa
脱ぎ捨てたら　さあ行こうよ　蜜の小川
Cast them off, and let's go to the other side.
That's right... There's somewhere I love.
seseragunami uneru kokan
せせらぐ波　うねる股間
The bubbling and undulating loins
ii kokan yudanesasete nametsudzukete kimi no riido
（良い股間）委ねさせて　舐め続けて　君のリード
What good loins, let me have and continue to lick your reed
There, I can see light through the trees.
I feel the soft wind.
And I hear the melody of the clarinet!
kaikan no tengoku
快感の天国
A heaven of pleasure.
ensoukai wo hajimeyou
演奏会を始めよう
Let us begin the recital.
There, I'll find the goddess of music.
odoru onpu jirasu rizumu airashikute
踊る音符　焦らすリズム　愛らしくて
The dancing stanzas and enticing rhythm lead us to love
At first I got hurt, and some
crazy things happened.
takaburu ai wo kanadeyou
昂ぶる愛を奏でよう
Let us play a melody of rising love,
iki wo awase yubi wo karame tamaranakute
息を合わせ　指を絡め　堪らなくて
locking hands and breathing as one.
But for some reason, I couldn't
take my eyes off her.
And now she's all I can think about!
koko wa miwaku no kajuen sa
ここは魅惑の果樹園さ
This is the garden of temptation.
kaburitsuku yo amai hakutou ureta meron
齧り付くよ　甘い白桃　熟れたメロン
I'll bite into the white peaches and wet melons.
koko wa erosu no resutoran
ここはエロスのレストラン
This is the restaurant of Eros.
hiwai na aji koosu ryouri gochisousama
卑猥な味　コース料理　ご馳走様
A full-course meal of lusty dishes...
okuchi ippai no niku no daichi
お口いっぱいの肉の大地
A full plate of delicious meat,
totemo guchuguchu shita sei no kajitsu
とてもぐちゅぐちゅした性の果実
of ripe sexual fruit.
yokei na mono nado iranai sa
余計なものなど要らないさ
I don't need anything else.
utsukushii yo sarakedashita kimi no ratai
美しいよ　曝け出した　君の裸体
Your exposed body is so beautiful,
tatoerarenai yorokobi sa
例えられない悦びさ
an indescribable happiness.
hajimari kara owaru shunkan zenbu hoshii
始まりから　終わる瞬間　全部欲しい
I want it all, from the beginning
to the moment it ends.
kimi no sono egao motto misete
君のその笑顔　もっと見せて
Show me more of your smile.
itsumo tsunagaritai doko ni ite mo
いつも繋がりたい　どこにいても
I want to be with you, wherever you are.
That's right, I...
sasete
させて
Let me do you.
Now, let me hear it...
What is this feeling?
My heart's pounding, and I'm so excited!
It's welling up inside me!
That's right, this is...
When I was little,
the first time I played the clarinet...
This is just like that.
Back then, my father smiled at me.
But now...
futari no
二人の
The two of us together,
kiseki wo
軌跡を
a miracle.
kasaneru ai
重ねる愛
Brought together by love...
ima koso motomeru eien no rakuen
今こそ求める　永遠の楽園
Here and now, an eternal Eden!
itsudemo soba ni iru
いつでも傍にいる
I'm by your side forever,
kokoro ni kimete
心に決めて
I've decided in my heart.
mou tamerawazu ni kono kimochi shinjitai
もう躊躇わずに　この気持ち信じたい
I want to believe in these feelings
with all my soul.
What is this?
massugu shoujiki ni
真っ直ぐ正直に
Let's look at each other
(shoujiki ni)
（正直に）
At each other
The lyrics are basically porn, but...
mitsumeteiyou
見つめていよう
Open and honestly
Why is it so...
I love it... I'm really feeling it!
The song, the lyrics, and this accompaniment...
sou kimi no hitomi kidzukasetekuretanda
そう君の瞳　気付かせてくれたんだ
Yes, you let me notice your eyes
One plus one plus one has
become five... Or ten...
No, a million!
It's a trinity of genius!
uruwashiki hana yo
麗しき花よ
A beautiful flower,
Fukune-chan...
yuri no saku sougen
百合の咲く草原
in a field of lilies.
Taketo...
hateshinaki ai yo
果てし無き愛よ
Share an endless love
kazoekirenai hodo ni
数え切れない程に
too many times to count...
hakanaku utsushidasu
儚く映し出す
An ephemeral reflection
(utsushidasu)
（映し出す）
Reflection.
ren'ai moyou
恋愛模様
of pictures of romance.
saa wakariaeru mirai ni chikattakara
さあ分かり合える　未来に誓ったから
Let's speak to one another,
because we swore to the future.
This is what...
What it means to play the clarinet!
I didn't know what to do...
I'm not a genius like everyone else.
So I didn't know what it was like
to enjoy something or to have fun.
Because I'm empty.
But... But...
This song...
Everyone's song is telling me...
The song is telling me who I am!
hoka ni ha nani mo iranai sa
他には何も要らないさ
We don't need anything else.
hadaka de katariaou
裸で語り合おう
Let's bare ourselves to one another.
I want to play more...
I want more people to hear!
shiawase wo tsuyoku dakishimete
幸せを強く抱き締めて
Embrace this happiness strongly
I love the clarinet!
S-So this is Miss Fukune.
futari wa ai no kiseki
二人は愛の奇跡
We are the miracle of love
This is a genius!
yume wa mugen hirogatteiku
夢は無限　広がっていく
Our dreams are endless,
They're people, too.
They stumble, they suffer,
they sometimes make mistakes.
yokubou no futari
欲望の二人
We are the essense of desire
But only because of that,
can they reach certain heights.
It's wonderful, don't you think?
futari no
二人の
The two of us together,
I'm leaving.
kiseki wo
軌跡を
a miracle.
kasaneru ai
重ねる愛
Brought together by love...
ima koso motomeru
今こそ求める
Here and now,
eien no rakuen
永遠の楽園
an eternal Eden!
And so...
The winner of the orientation tournament
is class 1-3!
Okay!
Taketo-kun...
T-Taketo-kun?
She just said "Taketo-kun"!
T-T-T-T-Taketo-kun!
Those lyrics...
What did they mean?
There were some parts I didn't understand.
Well, you see...
Someday...
Someday, I think you'll understand.
How idiotic.
Taketo!
Where do you want to go?
What about you, Fukune-chan?
Um...
Vienna!
I love you
Good work.
What do you mean by work?
Hmm?
I saw those two.
And I understood.
That's all.
Making everyone's dreams come true,
no matter when or where.
Don't you ever...
Nope!
I'm a genius idol!
But who will make your
dream come true?
I'm on my way to a concert.
A concert?
Where?
Vienna!
That's right...
Our school life has just begun!
Yup!
You know...
I didn't really expect you guys to win.
You really are geniuses.
Ask me whatever you want about Vienna...
Fukune-chan...
Do you get airsick?
If you say this formula I came up with
that calculates values from
cerebral biology and buoyancy,
your airsickness goes away immediately.
Let's do it together!
3.1415...
All done!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Thank you for watching ! !
-