I've never done anything
like this before.
I'll teach you everything,
Princess.
That's amazing!
Hurry! This way!
I've never done anything
like this before.
I'll teach you everything,
Princess.
Our first secret trip from the palace was
flavored with curiosity and danger.
An innocent girl, who knew nothing,
became an adult forever.
This was also a journey
to a world of ecstasy...
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Holiday Inspiration"
That doesn't quite work...
And a spinning bed?
A bit low-brow for this kind of story.
Indeed. Everyone is far too low-brow.
Oh, yeah...
Tomorrow's a day off, isn't it?
They've also given permission
to leave school grounds, right?
It's so unproductive to get worked up
over a single day off.
Of course, if the school's quiet,
that'd be the perfect time
to write my next paper.
But it might be nice to head
into the city, for once.
Sometimes, you need
to let yourself go...
L-Let yourself...
Y-You should be ashamed of yourself...
R-Ritsu, the formula!
3.14...
Are you going into town, Taketo-kun?
Utae-san.
You should try the crêpes from the
place in the central plaza.
They have lots of cream
and they're really yummy!
Cream...
Give me a taste...
That does sound good!
Taketo-kun, um, if you aren't busy...
Vacation Day
Date Spots
I never thanked you for before.
Would you like to go with me?
Oh, fine. If you really
want me to, I'll go.
Enjoying a little freedom
is part of being a kid.
It'd help with research for my novels...
Sorry, Utae-san... What were you saying?
Oh, nothing at all...
What is Narukara-san doing tomorrow?
Town?
Yup. We should take advantage
of this freedom.
And I've already researched
all the things we can do
to enjoy a little freedom as kids!
See? See? See?
We can shop for matching
accessories at the mall.
Or have tea at a café!
And we can talk and get to know
each other.
And then!
But I...
I know.
But you need to relax once in a while,
or you'll go nuts.
You really think so?
Ritsu, jeez...
He has me meet him this early
in the morning, and then he's late?
You're late!
Um... Hey...
So, Narukara-san, you're
going into town?
Yeah, of course. It is our day off.
You should relax.
Yes.
But you're bringing your clarinet...
I'm going back.
U-Um...
Sorry, Taketo. I couldn't
decide what to wear.
Hi, Fukune-chan!
Let's go and have fun!
What am I doing?
Stopping Narukara-san...
I've never done this before...
taking a day off to walk around town.
Oh yeah?
Practicing really keeps her busy.
She's so dedicated.
Welcome, welcome!
That's the place Utae-san mentioned.
Give us a taste!
It looks good!
No! I mean...
It's so sticky!
Oh, you silly thing.
Let's go eat.
Here you go. A vanilla
crêpe... 7,000,000 yen.
Um, my wallet...
I'll get it.
Th-Thanks.
So your boyfriend's buying it...
B-Boyfriend?!
It's good...
S-So cute!
Wait!
Where is she? Where? Where?
Where is Fukune-chan?
If she ended up with that pervert,
her chastity is in danger!
It's my job to make her blossom!
I found her!
We found you!
It's not like you to sit
here alone, Onee-sama.
That's right. We'll keep you company.
That's okay, isn't it? Onee-sama?
G-Girls...
Based on a statistical analysis
of his movement patterns,
as well as of the city's geographic data
and pedestrian flow,
Taketo will be...
Right here!
Huh?
Unexpected elements! Well, that's fine!
Everyone!
Your labor today forges
the Japan of tomorrow.
Let's all work hard!
Yeah!
Here I go.
I'm such a screw-up...
So the integral equals sigma over...
Y-You've got really great
lung capacity, Narukara-san.
I guess it's from playing
all that clarinet, huh?
A street musician?
She's really intense.
Narukara-san?
This is music, as well...
Where is he?
Taketo-kun...
I knew it!
It's Sonokoe Utae!
It's really her!
Amazing...
Wow, she's so cute...
P-Please shake my hand.
U-Um...
Sonokoe Utae?
Really?
And she'll shake your hand?
Then I'll go too!
Um... Everyone...
A celebrity's over there?
Who? Who is it?
Sh-Shiny!
What was all that?
Oh, man...
Are you okay, Narukara-san?
Here, use this.
Thanks.
W-Well...
For now, I guess we'll
have to wait out the rain.
I hope it stops soon.
Two hours' rest for 5,000 yen.
Do you think it will rain for two hours?
And what do you mean by 5,000 yen?
2 Hours' Rest
for 5,000 Yen
Hotel Amadeus?
Th-This is...
A l-l-l-l-l-love... Love... L-Love...
I-I honestly didn't mean
for this to happen.
I only came here because I didn't want
Narukara-san to catch a cold...
Seriously! I really mean it!
No, it isn't like that!
I never imagined Narukara-san would be
the first person I'd take to a hotel...
No, it isn't like that!
Then what is it like?
Why am I freaking out?
I've written about this a
hundred times in my novels!
I knew this would happen...
Um?
You looked like you were having fun.
You're silly, Akutagawa-kun.
You... You think so?
I'm kinda thirsty!
Maybe we should have some tea.
Nope! Not that!
Let's watch TV!
Video 1
What is this?
When I first saw it, I was
like, "Will this fit?"
Message Book
But when they put it
in, it felt great...
No, no, no!
You can't read that! At all!
This stuff's obscene.
But it's got a rawness to it.
Raw's good...
Raw is good?
That's right...
But I think euphemisms stimulate the
imagination more effectively.
I guess stuff's just better that way.
In a way, rawness is dangerous.
Narukara-san, I'm sorry.
That clarinet is really
important to you, right?
I wonder if I have something
that important, too...
No, no, no, no!
I can't say that. Absolutely not!
This is everything to me.
It was my first present from my dad.
My dad...
He's a famous clarinet player,
who performs all over the world.
Thanks, Dad—
Listen, Fukune...
Always remember this.
You don't choose music.
Music chooses you.
Those chosen by the music
are dubbed "geniuses".
Geniuses?
I'm sorry. I've never
told anyone that before.
N-No...
I'm the only one she's told!
So I guess that's how your father was.
He wanted you to be
really serious about music.
And you're doing it, so...
You're amazing, too. Yep...
Am I really?
I wonder why...
It's the same as usual,
but it feels kind of lonely.
H-Hey...
I-I need to say something.
I don't understand why, but she seems
worried about something.
But what should I say?
Nothing's coming to mind!
Normally, I can think of
all kinds of things to say!
All naughty things...
Why?
Narukara-san!
You're fine the way you are.
You know what's important to you.
So be confident... The
answer lies within you!
You're fine the way you are.
The answer to what's
important lies within you.
So be confident!
What a sleaze.
Who'd listen to that crap, anyway?
You couldn't get use out of that guy,
even if he were a cyborg.
It didn't work at all...
Let music be your sole thought, Fukune.
That's your life, as a genius.
I-I'm sorry!
Well, to be honest, um...
I just don't really know what to say.
Akutagawa-kun?
A-Anyway, all I can say now...
All I can say is...
I love your music!
I-I like hearing your clarinet!
Uh, i-if you stare at me like that...
I'm sorry. Are you mad?
U-Um...            U-Um...
I'm tired. Just really tired...
Wow! It's so pretty!
Well, I guess it's all right,
if Narukara-san is smiling.
Taketo!
I was looking for you for ages!
Where have you been?
You weren't alone with Narukara-san
the whole time, were you?
W-We just ran into each
other back there...
I'll reveal your lies
by asking Fukune-chan!
Are you okay? Did that ero-freak,
Taketo, do anything to you?
You can tell me the truth...
It's all his fault!
Y-Yeah, we just happened to meet there.
Really? That's great!
Oh, my...
This will be interesting.
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
I've never done anything
like this before!
Preview:
"Director of
X-Files"
This is Narukara Fukune.
I'm going to play shiritori again.
School Mizugi
"School swimsuit."
Giragira to kagayaku kemono no you na hitomi
"Eyes shining like a beast's."
Miro yo hora mou konna ni natte mattaku warui ko da kimi ha
Look at what's going on down there.
You're such a naughty girl.
haa, yamete
Oh, don't—