The room was empty.
The late evening sun gleaming through the windows, after the school's last bell,
with two people on the verge of breaking every rule possible...
Sensei,
I'll wait
in the
classroom,
af
ter
school.
Sensei,
I'll wait
in the
classroom,
af
ter
school.
Sensei,
I'll wait
in the
classroom,
af
ter
school.
Sensei,
I'll wait
in the
classroom,
af
ter
school.
Sensei,
I'll wait
in the
classroom,
af
ter
school.
Sensei,
I'll wait
in the
classroom,
af
ter
school.
Sensei,
Rational, common sense, and God Himself, had left his reasonings to his own.
His only thoughts were to plunge his newborn snake
deep into the slick, young underbrush.
Those thoughts alone commanded him.
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"Welcome to Inspiration Academy!"
A dream?
Working?
Or are you fantasizing again?
Try and keep your mouth zipped when having your delusions next time, okay?
No one wants to hear your thoughts,
Akutagawa Taketo-kun.
R-Right.
Excellent!
And there he goes again.
Splendid! He's like a beast,
overjoyed by springs onset!
A spring beast!
Taketo.
Your thoughts just never seem
to make any sense.
Jeez... not again.
Narukara-san...
U-Um...
Sensei! He's still acting just as bad...
Aw, man...
No, no. Calm down.
This is still a thousand times
better than middle school!
Ever since I revealed myself as the masked
porno author, pen named Akutagawa Taketo,
Masked
Porno
Author
Masked
Porno
Author
Akutagawa
Taketo
Debuts!!
no matter where I went,
people talked about me.
Behind my back and to my face.
Girls would cry, just because
I was in their class.
And I was called every kind of
awful name imaginable.
Ero-Fucker
Pervert Author
Every day was hell.
But now,
the reason I can enjoy even the semblance
of a high school life
is because of...
Inspiration Academy Private High School.
A sacred place of learning, for genius
students chosen from across Japan.
Tetsubou Meguru
Genius
Gymnast!!
Sparkling creativity.
Tetsubou Meguru
Genius
Gymnast!!
Minds and bodies in motion.
Spirits, as free as the wind.
Beni Batan
Genius
Avant-Garde Artist!
The possibilities are truly limitless.
Beni Batan
Genius
Avant-Garde Artist!
Beni Batan
Genius
Avant-Garde Artist!
Beni Batan
Genius
Avant-Garde Artist!
Beni Batan
Genius
Avant-Garde Artist!
Beni Batan
Decency, common sense, and ethics.
Musen Ran
None of the rules that apply
in the rest of the world,
Musen Ran
Genius
Programmer!
Musen Ran
Genius
Programmer!
can stem the tide of
their overflowing genius.
Meiki Raika
Genius
Photographer!
Because every boy and girl
here is a true genius!
Enshuu Ritsu
Genius
Mathematician!
These are the words of Kuroki Suiboku—founder,
principal, and school chairman,
"Genius is 1% inspiration
and 99% perspiration!"
In other words,
believe in your inspiration,
and fight to the end!
Perspiration, without
inspiration, is wasted!
No matter what others say,
ignore them!
This is the Inspiration Academy's motto,
"Trust your inspiration! Trust your talent!
Follow your own path!"
Glory to Inspiration Academy!
Trust your inspiration!
Trust your talent!
Follow your own path!
This is Kiya Star, narrating!
Kiya Star
Genius
Narrator
She's a genius.
But sometimes geniuses do
make mistakes, too.
Listen, Taketo.
I'm your classmate and friend.
I'd like to think that I'm making a
real attempt to understand your talent.
But given that female students don't understand
and continue to misunderstand you...
It's, well...
I can't bear to watch it.
To be honest,
you're too wide-open!
Taketo?
Are you listening?
No one understands.
Blinded by a superficial sense
of morality and disgust,
they've lost sight of the truth.
After all...
sex lies at the core of human existence!
Thus, to write about sex is to write
about what makes us truly human!
Yes, that is the literature of which I pen!
Using my prowess as a pornographic writer,
I shall someday reach the very heights of literature!
And when my literature
touches the heart of mankind...
No, on the day I carve
my name into literary history,
"Between Warmth and Wetness"
by Akutagawa Taketo.
Best Seller!
Huge new print run!!
the world will change!
When I triumph over those who mocked me,
it will be a day of glory!
Akutagawa Taketo Wins
The Tokyo Governor's Prize
I'll live richly off the royalties!
I'll have beautiful girls
and a sunny island,
and I'll enjoy life in my palace of sin!
Hey, Taketo!
Are you listening?
Y-Your eyelashes are too long!
I mean, I'm listening. I'm listening.
Yeah, wide-open... that's it.
I'm too wide-open. I'd like to think that's it.
I mean, I like you...
Y-You like me?
What are you talking about?
I'm just your classmate.
So...
Ritsu?
But I... I definitely don't, okay?
Calm down, Ritsu!
Here, let me write this out again.
What does this equal?
3.141592653589793238462643...
He looks like he takes things seriously,
but he's actually really sincere and nice.
But why does he
say nonsensical things sometimes?
Here you go, Onee-sama. Open up!
How is it?
It's good!
Aa-chan, your ebi-fry is so delicious,
it echoes throughout the galaxy!
Come to think of it, Ritsu once said
that Ran...
It's so sweet.
Onee-sama, I'm embarrassed.
Let's see how it tastes down here.
Well, I'm not the kind of guy to
complain about anyone else's tastes.
Ow!
Stop looking at us! Creep!
Hold on a second.
It isn't like he said something.
There's no reason to behave that way.
What did Taketo do to you?
He looked at us! In a lewd way!
I bet he was thinking of
perverted things again.
And I don't think he has
the right to even use my name!
So are you a psychic genius?
If nothing else, I'd need a more
logical answer than that.
What?
What?!
Ritsu, I'm grateful
for your friendship,
but I actually was imagining
things. I'm sorry.
Ch-Chief!
Chief of what?
You don't know her?
She's the Newspaper Circle Chief.
She's a first-rate genius,
even here at Inspiration Academy.
Taketo-san, we've decided on the
front page, for next week's paper.
"New Freshman Special!
Watch out for these geniuses!"
New First-Years
Featured Report!
Take notice of
this First-year!
First
Section
"The Clarinet Genius"
Narukara
Fukune
Profile
H
W
D.O.B.
"Part 1: Narukara Fukune,
Clarinet Genius."
Fukune-chan?
So the first one will be from our class?
This'll be interesting.
Um, Chief, I'm sorry.
But I don't know if it's a good idea for me
to conduct the interview this time...
Is there some problem?
Um, well...
Kind of... Sort of...
Ow.
Take care of it for me, okay?
U-Um, Chief!
She isn't in the classroom
nor in the music wing.
And she's not back at
her dorm, which means...
You really are looking for
her, Akutagawa Taketo.
You're almost like a
stalker. Stalker boy.
I can't help it! I have to interview her
for the Newspaper Circle.
I guess with that as your excuse,
you can do whatever you want.
Good for you, pervert.
Why are you following me, anyway?
You're not part of the Newspaper Circle.
They want me to take some pictures.
You didn't know that
much? EroEro-head-kun.
Come on, show me what you really are.
What I really am?
I want a moment of ugliness and lust.
In that moment, you can see
what humans really are.
What's wrong? Come on, do it...
Stop it, you stupid insect!
I'm the camerawoman here!
No, tonight we'll be
taking pictures of you.
I know who I'm making
as my personal page #1...
M-My eyes!
That face was pretty
good, you centipede.
Walking failure...
"The man put his black-red madness
to her quivering honey pot.
'Haan...'
Pleasure juice overflowed.
It was hotter than magma
and sweeter than cream,
and yet, it had the bitterness of sin.
And the camerawoman..."
Hey, stop it! Don't read that!
What? You were thinking about me?
Well, keep it up.
Don't miss a chance to let
your instincts go crazy.
Why are you sitting there?
Hurry up, ero-freak!
Whose fault is this?
But she's right. This is a chance.
I need to get off my butt.
I want to talk to Narukara-san.
I want a real chance to talk with her.
And I want to apologize.
I love you!
I love you, summer days!
No matter how much time goes by,
I'll always remember you.
First Love Memories!
Sonokoe Utae
Genius
Idol Singer
I can't take my eyes
off you for a second!
If she isn't anywhere I've looked,
where could she be?
Stay away! Stay away! Stay away!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Kagaku Tsukuru
Genius
Inventor
The output was just fine, too...
Maybe it's the balance...
Guess I'll work on the
wing design some more...
What is this? Some kind of nut, maybe?
It smells good.
It's kind of damp...
What are you doing...
Um, well...
I was a little hungry.
And I didn't get enough sleep,
so I kind of spaced out...
My reed...
N-No!
D...
Da?
Don't eat it!
I-I wasn't going to!
A dream?
Is that it?
Ta-dah!
Go! Go, Inspiration!
Let's go, Inspiration!
Fight! Fight! Yay!
That's right. This is where I...
And Narukara-san...
Wh-What am I doing, staring at her?
This is my chance!
I can talk to her without Raika here.
I-It's simple, right?
What's this feeling?
Wh-What am I doing?
Stop! Stop it!
I...
Wh-What did I write?
What are you doing?
No, well... that's...
A defenseless girl is sleeping there,
right in front of you!
Go on and devour her, already!
Like a hungry pig!
Go on! Charge! Let out a big,
old "oink", you puberty pig!
And you call yourself
a perverted teenager?
You should be ashamed of yourself!
You ****!
That's what you're mad about?
What is that?
No, well...
"If you were to give it a name, you could
call it the purest drop, the gold drop."
The gold drop...
"A lustrous jewel, made from
the life and the beauty of spring.
That was..."
What is this?
Don't read it! Just don't read it!
This isn't what you write!
You should be writing about her
woman-bush or something!
Or a gleaming spear of flesh!
Or a pea! Stuff like that!
Have you gone mad, Taketo?
Just what are you even saying?
Rape! Violate! Mons pubis! Repeat!
Get back to being yourself!
Rape! Violate! Mons pubis! Say it!
I-I'm not saying that!
Rape... Violate...
Mons pubis...
Listen! You're...
A-Again?!
Narukara-san?
U-U-U-Um....
No!
N-Narukara-san, wait...
I ended up with bigger problems
than that interview.
But what was that, anyway?
I've never felt anything like that before.
It was unlike anything else.
It was energetic and overpowering,
but somehow clear.
No, it was more...
more... I don't know.
What's the use of just
thinking about this?
I'm an author! There is but
one thing for me to do,
write!
Transforming with my magic clarinet!
Purarara Purarira Pururupi!
I'll never stop blowing!
Magical Girl Fukune-chan!
"Purarira... Pururupi..."
Wh-What is this?
Why am I writing a light novel?
Th-This hasn't ever happened before.
What hasn't?
Chief!
Taketo-san! Is your draft ready?
Um, well...
Wait. There's a reason for this.
Actually, why are you
in the guy's dorms?
If it's not done, that
can't be helped, I guess.
I'll wait as long as it takes for you to
write me something good, Akutagawa-sensei!
Ch-Chief...
Did you think I'd say that?
No...
No way!
One more!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
N-No!
Don't look!
It's me, Narukara Fukune.
Preview:
"An Idol Even if I Strip!"
I'll play shiritori.
Furume
"Wife..."
Medaka
"Ricefish..."
Kaiawase
"Scissoring"
Sensei...ja
"Sensei, stop. This isn't what
I intended..."
Ja...
"Then what's going on
down here?"