What was that breeze?
It felt like someone tried to lift up my skirt.
It's no good...
I can't count the thousands of pornos
I've written that originated in panty shots.
No! I must find some new inspiration!
Is your draft done?
Ch-Chief!
Um, well... N-Not yet.
My phone!
Yes? Right now.
No, I understand.
Yes, I won't miss more deadlines.
Yes... Yes, I'll do my best!
Are you in some kind of slump?
Yes...
Doki!! to shi chau! daisuki da!
DOKI！！っとしちゃう！　大スキDA！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
Atama no naka juugo no himitsu seifuku ni KAKU-RETAA
アタマの中十五の秘密　せーふくに書く-レター
These fifteen secrets in my head are written in letters, tucked away in my uniform.
Kimi ga guru-guru shichau IMEEJI no kidou-chuu
キミがグルグルしちゃう　イメージの起動中
When you keep on making circles around me, in the middle of the launch of your image,
Ijiwaru-me ni yasashiku shite houbaru hitokuchi
イジワルめに優しくして　ほーばる一口
you treat me kindly even with your mean look and puffed cheeks.
Kitto ookiku! Shichau hajimete no Doki☆Doki
きっとおーきく！シちゃう　初めてのドキ☆ドキ
For your first heart-throbbing, I'm sure you'll find it tremendous!
Koe ga dechau YODAITAN ♪
声が出ちゃうよ、ダイタン♪
Your voice will escape daringly!
Kyun to shitai no oshiete!
きゅんとしたいの　教えて！
What you want to make your heart tingle, tell me!
Hayaku! Sasete! Doko de? Nani wo? ! Maji yaba!
はヤく！　さセて！　ドコで？　ナニヲ？！　マジヤバ！
Quick! Let me! Where do you want what?! Seriously, you're terrible!
Mousou bakuhatsu!
もーそうバクハツ！
These wild ideas have all detonated!
Motto tabete mitai
もっと食べてみたいっ
I want to try and swallow more
motto nadete hoshii
もっとなでて欲しいっ
I want you to pet me more
Kimi no haato donna o aji?!
キミのハートどんなお味ぃ?!
What kind of flavor is your heart?
Itsuka kitto tsukamu riaru
いつかきっとつかむリアル
Someday, I'll be sure to grasp a hold of what's real
Motto daite mitai
もっと抱いてみたいっ
I want to embrace you more
Sotto misete mo ii?
そっと 見せてもいぃ？
Will you secretly let me see you?
Yume no naka ja mono tan NAI no☆
夢の中じゃ物足んないの！☆
I can't get enough of this dream I'm having!
Kokoro karada iiyo agechau kimi dakara
ココロ＆カラダ　いいよっ　アゲちゃう　キミだから
Be it my heart or also my body, I'll hand them over since it's you.
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you! (Look here!)
Sora!
そら！
Doki to shichau daisuki DA!
ドキッとしちゃう　大スキダ！！
My heart throbs as I really do love you!
"What If Inspiration Academy's Genius Manager..."
Middle School Softball Tournament Championship!
Three outs! That ends the inning!
Another scoreless inning for Nagano.
This is the final game of last year's national
middle-school softball tournament.
On one side, was a very experienced team.
And on the other, a team which had never
made it past the preliminaries.
Which won, do you think?
The experienced team, right?
Middle School Softball Tournament Championship!
And that's the game!
In their first appearance,
Sumikawa Middle School wins!
Nope.
And she's their secret.
Who?
The genius manager who can lead any team,
no matter how weak, to victory!
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Kurabu Katsuyo.
Kurabu Katsuyo
Genius
Manager
Taketo...
Wh-What is this?
Okay, you two have fun!
Ch-Chief!
Welcome to the canned-in room.
You have forty-eight hours left,
no matter what.
You can't miss the deadline again.
So, let the game begin!
But I'm sure it'll be fine.
I believe in you, Akutagawa-sensei.
Let's get to work!
Yeah, I know...
This isn't how literary people work.
I'm sorry. I had the wrong idea...
I'm an idiot!
It's fine. Seriously, it's fine.
That's right.
Just because I'm in a slump,
I can't let myself get down.
Akutagawa-sensei!
I need to put my back into it. Yeah!
That's a relief...
I always work with sports clubs.
This is my first cultural club,
so I was a bit worried.
Akutagawa-sensei...
Let's both do our best!
Stop calling me sensei.
Taketo is fine.
Then you can call me Katsuyo!
All right, Katsuyo-chan.
Thank you!
Well, regardless of how it happened, she's here to support me.
But I'm a bit worried, given that
the chief brought her into this.
Come to your desk.
I prepared paper and writing utensils for you.
If there's anything you need, just ask. Okay?
O-Okay!
Canned Beef
Noon : 2 Hours Have Passed
I'll go change, okay?
Ch-Change?
Then, beyond that door...
Th-This is...
No good. I've got nothing.
Normally, this would be enough for 40 pages.
I've gotta write. I have columns,
short stories, books...
There's no time!
What if I can't write anymore?
L-O-V-E... Akutagawa!
C-U-T-E... Taketo, yay!
I'm happy, but be quiet.
1:00 PM : 3 Hours Have Passed
Did you hear, Onee-sama?
What?
About Akutagawa Taketo.
He's out because he has deadlines, right?
I heard he's in a slump, and he's locked in
somewhere until his work's done.
I like it better with him gone. It's quiet.
But I hope he'll take this chance
to become a normal human being.
Locked up?
All right!
I thought an apron and uniform
was a clichéd trope,
but maybe I should rethink that.
Taketo-kun?
Lunch is almost done. So wait just a bit, okay?
I've got it!
No, I don't...
It's done!
A-Already?
Huh? Was it too soon?
No... Thanks.
I've never eaten a girl's
home-cooked meal before.
Eat a lot, and build up your stamina.
Okay!
Eat it while it's hot.
What is that?!
Katsuyo's special tuna eyeball stew!
It's good brain food!
Eat up!
Taketo-kun?
What's wrong, Taketo-kun?
Taketo-kun!
Katsuyo-kun!
Y-Yes?
What organ of the human body can swell,
up to six times its normal size?
What organ?
Th-The peni—
You fool!
Watch your language!
I-I'm sorry!
The eye!
Huh?
It gets bigger when it's dark...
When it's dark?
Y-Yes!
Then let's check your answer!
Good morning!
Raika?
If you've got time to sleep,
I guess you're doing fine.
Don't you have deadlines to meet?
Oh, man! I slept a long time!
Thank you for waking me!
I need to hurry...
Don't worry about it.
I just came to photograph the
porno author who can't write porno.
Good morning, Taketo-kun!
Kurabu Katsuyo?
Welcome back.
Are you hungry?
Just wait. I'll get dinner ready.
Thanks.
Taketo...
Do you know who she is?
A genius manager, right?
I was told that anyone she helps
will succeed, no matter what.
That's right. Having her on your side
essentially means success.
But that victory always comes with a price.
Here's what ended up happening to
the baseball team with whom she worked.
That's my phone? How...
Yes?
Oh, me? I'm Taketo-san's manager,
Kurabu Katsuyo.
Taketo-san?
One minute...
It's your publisher.
I'm not here! Tell them I'm not here!
He said, "Tell them I'm not here."
I'm very sorry. No, please...
Listen to me!
My PC's having problems...
Oh, I hand write, don't I?
Um, then something happened to a relative...
I got some great photos!
Good luck with your writing.
No more... I can't go on.
Taketo-kun?
I'm a terrible writer! I'm sure that's
what the editor thinks...
That's not true! I know you can do it.
Get back your self-confidence!
That's right!
It's my hand's fault!
I have to write because I have hands!
Wait! T-Taketo-kun, don't!
I have deadlines because I have hands!
I see. She even practices this late.
Maybe I'll try a bit harder.
No!
No, Taketo-kun!
Taketo-kun!
8:00 AM : 22 Hours Have Passed
No way!
You don't have to force yourself to read them.
No! As your manager, I should be
familiar with all your work.
No way... No!
D-Don't!
I didn't think I'd have to listen
to that all night...
Keep going. Do your best...
As hard as you can.
I'm glad she's cheering me on,
even in her dreams...
Oh, I'm sleepy, too.
Taketo!
I heard from Raika
that you were locked in here
with your manager...
Oh, Ritsu. Sorry. Let them know
I won't be in today, okay?
My schedule's really rough...
R-Rough?
Yeah, really rough.
They've been riding me pretty hard.
Riding you hard?
Gan
I-I'm sure with your talent,
you'll be fine. But...
I-I-I...
Ritsu! Recite pi!
3.1415926535...
No... I'm falling asleep..
Katsuyo-kun!
Y-Yes?
Give me the name of a
northern Saskatchewan lake!
O...
Well?
O-Oman...
Louder!
Oman... Lake.
Oman Lake!
More passion!
Like you're whispering secrets
in your lover's ear!
Oman Lake...
Like you've just had an orgasm!
Oman Lake!
Like when you're drinking coffee at dawn...
What's this?
I'll talk to
the teacher.
Good luck.
Ritsu...
Thanks, Ritsu.
Now then, back to work.
Yes?
Again?!
This is pornographic author
Akutagawa Taketo's phone.
If you're calling regarding anything
other than a deadline extension,
please leave a message after the beep!
Beep!
Perfect!
Don't answer my phone!
I-I'm sorry! I thought that
just because I'm your manager...
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
And one more bonus idiot!
She has problems.
She has serious problems...
Noon : 26 Hours Have Passed
I'm hungry...
Katsuyo-chan? It's open!
Excuse me.
I stopped by.
Utae-san?
I heard it's really hard on authors
when they have a deadline.
So I made you a lunch.
Should I not have?
No, I'm really glad you did!
I was just getting hungry.
Oh, my... I'm embarrassed.
I hurried because I didn't have much time.
Utae-san...
That's right. She's an idol, isn't she?
She's busy, but she still found time for me...
A real boxed lunch, from the
world's most famous idol.
Complete with bandage toppings.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry...
I never knew it was so wonderful
having someone support you...
Y-You're exaggerating, Taketo-kun.
Let's eat.
O-Okay!
You have no time, right?
Keep writing, and I'll feed you.
Say "ahh"!
Ahh...
This is kind of embarrassing.
Y-Yeah.
S-So, how is it?
It's great!
Really?
Really! Really!
It's the best boxed lunch I've ever had!
You're exaggerating.
Good luck with your writing, sensei!
Say "ahh"!
Ahh...
Th-These are definitely her chopsticks.
Wh-Which means...
Her lips were on them.
And they're touching my lips...
So my lips are on hers?
This is incredible!
I can do this!
I can put this passion into my writing...
I'm back...
I'm sorry. One of the sports clubs
wanted my help.
But I'm done now.
What a wonderful lunch!
Who made it?
W-Would you like to join us?
Are you sure?
Thanks. I'm really hungry.
Canned Beef
G-Good luck...
Th-Thanks.
Thanks for lunch!
Bye!
I was so close to getting something...
How is it? Still nothing?
Yeah. Nothing.
But that's okay!
You have twenty hours, so um...
How many per hour...
How many pages do you need to write?
That's it! If you want to entice someone,
you need concealment!
Then, once it's time, a glimpse of exposure!
Everyone knows that!
Concentrate...
This emotion I feel, with all my senses...
I'll be able to put this passion
into my words this time!
You were peeking, weren't you?
N-No! My eyes just moved on their own...
It's for your work, isn't it?
I've read a lot of your books, so I understand.
You need stuff like this for your work, right?
Okay, then...
Bang!
No. That's not it...
That isn't what I need!
9:00 PM : 35 Hours Have Passed
Twelve hours left. How's it coming?
Are you done?
Not at all.
Fine. I guess I have no choice!
From now on, you cannot look away from
your paper, even for a second.
Let's write! I'll do my best, too!
Fight, oh! Fight, oh! Let's go...
That again, huh?
Sweat.
Here you go, sensei.
Th-That's not it!
M-My hand...
Please... use your hands to work a miracle!
That isn't it, either!
Well? Are you done?
No good. I can't write girls anymore.
Oh, no... Even these clothes
I saved didn't work?
It's okay. I'm going to stop being a writer.
You can't do that!
You're a genius porno writer...
You have to write porno!
I can't.
You can't give up!
I can't do it!
I can't write! Not after you've done all this!
B-But I'm your manager...
That's enough! Get out!
I'm sorry...
Was that too harsh?
But it's fine. It's over.
Taketo-kun?
I've got it this time!
You can't write because I'm a girl,
so I had an idea.
Everyone!
The Genius Academy Muscle Circle Premium Muscle!
Muscler!
Okay, everyone!
Show Taketo-kun how wonderful men are,
so he can write his porno!
We are muscle!
Yo! Biceps!
Yo! Abs!
Pecs!
Well, Taketo-kun?
They're touching me... They're touching me!
Hard! But wet...
And stinky!
Do your best, Akutagawa-sensei!
I can't! I can't do it!
This isn't why I came here.
M-My memories are flashing before my eyes?
Good luck...
Yo! Muscle!
G-Girls!
Inspiration
City
Shopping
District
A new era for Akutagawa Taketo!!
The lust and passion of Heaven and Hell
Beyond the
Wall of Flesh
Novels
Taketo hasn't come back yet.
He probably got arrested, don't you think?
He's in the hospital, due to fatigue.
It must've been really hard...
The hospital?
Scary... Scary!
Muscle is scary!
No men!
Taketo-kun...
I had them come back!
Muscle!
No men!
General Hospital
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA eiyou busoku
ほら、ヒラメキパワー栄養不足
Hey there, that FLASHY POWER needs more energy!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE joushou chuu!
またバンザイして、ＰＥＡＣＥ上昇チュー！
Shout HURRAY, and raise the words of PEACE to the sky!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Yeah!
sa, ikou asaichi kara HAPPII ai KNOW shoubu shitagi dashii
さ、行こう朝一からハッピー、愛ＫＮＯＷ勝負下着だしー
Come, be HAPPY first thing in the morning; love KNOWS the outcome of the underwear battle!
naisho! Punipuni shita kanjii, nanige sugoindesu
内緒！プニプニして感じー、何気すごいんです
Hold on! Keep this a secret, it feels awfully squishy down below; it feels amazing.
chotto miteiru kara daarin
ちょっと見ているから、ダーリン
Since you're taking a peek, darling,
douzo agemashou ka, baajin!
どうぞあげげましょうか、バージン！
shall I give you myself, you virgin!
otto, koufun shicha WARNING sore mo OKAY!
おっと、興奮しちゃＷＡＲＮＩＮＧ，それもＯＫＡＹ
Oh my, you WARNING me about your arousal? I'm OKAY with that!
KIRA☆KIRA kyoushitsu no RAKUEN issho ni tobidasou
キラ☆キラ教室のラクエン一緒に飛び出そう
Let's jump into the heaven that is a sparkling room!
SAY EVERYBODY kaikan deribaa RE:
ＳＡＹ　ＥＶＥＲＹＢＯＤＹ　快‐感デリバーＲＥ：
SAY EVERYBODY, we can reply to our pleasant feelings.
hashire chaimu De: Play ball!
走れ、チャイムＤＥ：　ＰＬＡＹ　ＢＡＬＬ！
It's time to run and PLAY BALL!
Yay!
ikouyo! BANZAI☆PEACE! akiramenaide PEACE!
行こうよ！バンザイ☆PEACE！あきらめないでＰＥＡＣＥ！
Let's go! Long live PEACE! Don't give up PEACE!
kitto kyou mo E koto aru hazu
きっと今日もＥコトあるはず
Today we'll surely have 'ecchi' moments,
te wo agetara JANPU! HIGH-TENSION na kami-sama, chuumoku
手を上げたらジャンプ！ＨＩＧＨ－ＴＥＮＳＩＯＮな神様、注目！
Raise your hands and JUMP! God of HIGH-TENSION, beware!
Yay!
mo iccho! BANZAI☆PEACE! daijobu da yo PEACE!
もいちょー！バンザイ☆PEACE！ダイジョブだよＰＥＡＣＥ！
Once more! Long live PEACE! Everything is all right, PEACE!
mottou waratte itsudemo kaisei
もっとー笑って、いつでも快晴
Laugh and smile more, it'll always be sunny
hyakuten Nan-DA jishin manman de mune hatterya E tte koto!
百点ナンダ、自身満々で胸張ってりゃＥってコト！
Full marks! When I'm confident with my bosoms, I'll leave you a wonderful 'ecchi' feeling!
Yay!
hora HIRAMEKI PAWAA SUKIPPU shite seiretsu
ほら、ヒラメキパワースキップして整列
See here, SKIP that FLASHY POWER and line up!
mata BANZAI shite PEACE! koushin da; rettsu GO!
またバンザイしてＰＥＡＣＥ！行進だ、レッツＧＯ！
Shout HURRAY and PEACE! It's a parade, let's go!
hai yeah
tarata tattara tattarata
foo foo~
tatta taratta
Today's Nosebleed Gauge
Tamaya!
Let's take a break.
Preview:
"Girl's Academy"
It's me, Kurabu Katsuyo!
Last out, bottom of the ninth!
It's just like...
B-Balls... They're...
So big! So big...
C-Coming!
It's in—